[Music]
[Música]
k
k
ah
ah
[Music]
[Música]
a
un
in [Music] [Music]
en
ma Okay, let's leave it here, okay, how are you
ma Bueno vamos a dejarlo por aquí vale
family? How are you? How are you?
qué tal familia Cómo estáis qué tal
Well, first of all, have you seen
Bueno antes que nada habéis visto el
today's episode? Did you like it a lot?
episodio de hoy os ha gustado mucho lo
Have you
habéis
enjoyed it? How are you?
disfrutado qué tal estáis
Tell me how are you?
contadme qué tal
How are we? Does it sound good?
estáis qué tal estamos se escucha bien
Hello, hello, trying out a two
Hola hola probando un dos
TR. Good night everyone. Good night,
TR buenas noches a todos Buenas noches
I saw it, it was a gem. Hey, today's is one of the ones that's
yo lo vi fue una joya Oye es de los que
working best.
está funcionando mejor el de hoy eh el
Today's is one of the ones that's working best
de hoy es de los que está funcionando
on the
mejor en la
list. What a shame. It's going to give me a hard time when it's
lista qué lástima Me va a dar cuando se
over. What a shame. It's going to give me a
acabe
hard time if it's over. uh,
eh Qué lástima me va a dar si se acaba
when it's over, no, it will end at
eh cuando se acabe no que se acabará en
some point, obviously. What a shame. What a shame. What a shame. How many are left? Well, there are
algún momento evidentemente Qué pena Qué
few left. There are few left. But,
faltan pocos faltan pocos pero pero
well, there's still something to enjoy because there are some
bueno todavía hay para disfrutar porque
left. Look, I'm going to tell you.  teach I
faltan Mira os lo voy a enseñar se lo
showed it to you before your honor I don't mind
enseñé antes la señoría no me importa
showing it to you
enseñároslo a ustedes
too because I already have them here
también porque ya los tengo aquí
prepared
preparados
prepared okay they are here we are
preparados vale están aquí estamos
talking about this is
hablando de este es el de
today's this is today's tomorrow is this I
hoy este es el de hoy mañana es este me
sneak into Francua's Setup this is
cuelo en el Setup de francua este está
very good eh Also tomorrow's is
muy bueno eh También el de mañana está
very
muy
good tomorrow's is very good
bueno el de mañana está muy bueno
Look let's gossip with Fran the Setup This
Mira vamos a cotile a Fran el Setup Esta
is Fran's house it literally costs
es la casa de Fran cuesta literalmente
okay literally I sneak in so that
vale literalmente me meto que no entrre
the
las
nutri doesn't enter I literally sneak into
nutri literalmente me cuelo en el Setup
Francua's Setup okay and I gossip about it there and that one
de francua vale y le cotilleo por ahí y
was today actually because
ese ese era hoy en verdad porque
chronologically This was before
cronológicamente Esto fue antes que lo
today's what happens is that I made a mistake and I gave
de hoy lo que pasa que me equivoqué y le
the editor this one before okay But tomorrow
di al editor este antes vale Pero mañana
comes
viene
this one already passed comes the one from the
este ya pasado viene el el de el de la
jungle of Fran this one is going to be long the
selva de Fran este este va a ser largo
one from the jungle is going to be long the truth is
el de la selva va a ser largo la verdad
this gave to divide it in two
este daba para dividirlo en dos las
things as they are this gave to divide it
cosas como son este daba para dividirlo
in two
en dos
but I'm going to leave it at one the truth is I'm
pero lo voy a dejar en uno la verdad lo
going to leave it at one this is that Fran took me
voy a dejar en uno esto es que Fran me
jungle In position in position I have
selva En posición en posición he
checked
revisado
everything
todo
damn it's like the one from the  Cristina as well
[__] es como el de la Cristina así
as DEA Thanks
como DEA Gracias
cool guy I love it I love it dude
tío chulo me encanta me encanta tío
Thank you very much yesterday I saw it la crisa di
Muchas gracias ayer se lo vi la crisa di
Guay how comfortable this is
Guay que comodito esto
no well where are we going the selv
no bueno dónde vamos la
jungle with Fran de la Cuesta okay
selv selva con Fran de la cuesta vale
listen to me Okay says wizard Javi if
escúchame Vale dice wizard Javi si
later you upload a compilation video of
después subes un vídeo recopilatorio de
the whole series to see what what there is is what I
toda la serie a ver lo que lo que hay es
'm telling you okay the one with the
esto que os estoy diciendo vale el de la
snake was today tomorrow the one with the
serpiente ha sido hoy mañana el del
Setup the day after the one with the
Setup pasado el de la
jungle I don't know if I should stop it on Saturday no and not
selva no sé si pararlo el sábado no y no
upload anything on Saturday no because Saturday
subir nada el sábado no porque el sábado
is a bad day no maybe not eh And then there's
es mal día no a lo mejor no eh Y luego
the last episode which is the
queda el último episodio que es la
farewell The farewell to the sanctuary in which
despedida La despedida del santuario que
some moments
aquí se van a recopilar algunos momentos
and such will be compiled okay
y demás vale
eh And then Probably what I'll do let's
eh Y luego Probablemente lo que haga a
see Today is Thursday
ver Hoy es jueves
not Thursday Friday Saturday and
no jueves viernes sábado y
Sunday I'll probably do
domingo es probable que haga
one of the entire series in one
uno de la serie entera en un
video I'll probably do one of the
vídeo es probable que haga uno de la
entire jungle of the entire jungle of the
entera de la selva entera de la serie
entire series I don't know how long it will last okay it will be
entera no sé cuánto durará vale será
like the full report okay I'll
como el reportaje completo vale Es
probably put it together but well if
probable que lo una en una pero bien si
the intro like that I'll do it well okay And then
la intro tal lo haré bien vale Y luego
as I promised you
como ya os prometí
[Music]
[Música]
the  from Disneyland Hong
el de Disneyland Hong
Kong hello family how are you
Kong muy buenas familia Qué tal estáis
okay Welcome to another video this
bueno Bienvenidos a otro vídeo este
little video that we are recording for you from
videíto que os estamos grabando desde
Hong Kong Look at the views we have around
Hong Kong Mirad qué vistas tenemos por
here Okay Lu I'm going to try to show it to you
aquí Bueno Lu a intentar enseñároslo por
tonight when we get ready but
la noche cuando nos recojamos pero
basically This video is going to be
básicamente Este vídeo pues va a ser
like
como
an extra episode after the trip to
un episodio extra después del viaje a
Thailand and that week that we spent
Tailandia y esa semana que hemos pasado
with Fran from the jungle because in this at
con Fran de la jungla porque en este en
this moment while we
este instante mientras que nosotros
are here living this
estamos aquí viviendo esto
you Let's see I'm going to put some
ustedes A ver os voy a poner algún
spoilers not some little thing no Let's see what I
spoiler no alguna cosilla no A ver cuál
can put for you because I don't know so
os puedo poner es que no sé así al
randomly what I show you
azar cuá los
this
este
eye
ojo
[Music] eye ​​eye
[Música]
Hey well Oh the castle Where is the
Eh bueno Ay el castillo Dónde está el
castle Where is the castle
castillo Dónde está el castillo
recorded the Disney one you're going to love the
grabado el de Disney os va a encantar la
truth is that the Disney one is very nice
verdad que el de Disney está muy guapo
very very nice
muy muy guapo
[Music]
[Música]
eh What do I put because I don't want to give any
eh Qué pongo que tampoco quiero hacer
spoilers either
spoilers
[Music]
[Música]
impotent is the train
impotent es el tren
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
already
ya
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
Hello Me  nice to see you again to think
Hola Me alegro de verte de nuevo pensar
that I've been seeing you since I was 16 and I'm already 21
que te veo desde los 16 y ya tengo 21
How time flies haha ​​Kisses crack
Cómo pasa el tiempo jaja Besos crack
How
Cómo
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
passes
pasa
this one is very cool the one from dis
este va está muy chulo el de dis
eh
eh
Give me the
Dame la
[Music]
[Música]
wallet I wanted to show you the castle
cartera quería enseñaros el castillo
but I
pero
can't
no
find it let's see
encuentro a ver
this ño
este ño
ño saac what I saw from Agustín He
ño saac lo que vi de Agustín Es que le
made things very clear to ar
dejó las cosas bien claritas a ar
Gameplay eh he said Don't mess with me
Gameplay eh le dijo No te metas conmigo
because I know I mean it's not said in these
porque yo sé O sea no se dicho con estas
words but I understand it because I
palabras pero yo lo entiendo porque yo
know some things that are not known okay
sé algunas cosas que no se saben vale
but I'm sure I know that
pero seguro que se
basically Agustín 51 made it
eso básicamente Agustín 51 le dejó
clear to
clarito a
Ari I have things that I have things that are
Ari tengo cosas que tengo cosas que son
very
muy
[Music]
[Música]
strong no no no neurofunk there are things
fuertes no no no neurofunk hay cosas del
about Ari and others that are not known Okay and
tema Ari y demás que no se saben Vale y
Agustín who is a friend of gref said I don't know
Agustín que es amigo de gref dijo No sé
how he messes with me knowing
cómo se mete conmigo sabiendo
that I can see her destroy Neither
que que la puedo a ver destruir Tampoco
because Nor do I think it's anything
porque Tampoco tampoco creo que sea nada
that matters
que enda
but let's look at the
pero vamos a mirar el
castle the Hong Kong blog is  as
castillo el blog de Hong Kong es como ya
the closure is
el cierre
not missing the bridge man I would have
no me falta el puente tío me hubiera
missed a bridge here
faltado aquí un puente la
[Music]
[Música]
truth Fernando does not know I have not
verdad Fernando no lo sabe no se lo he
told him I would feel it like
dicho lo sentiría como la
betrayal
traición
[Music]
[Música]
that Disney is more expensive Javi it ​​is the
es más caro ese Disney Javi es
same it is the same in Hong Kong more or less
igual es igual en Hong Kong más o menos
I would say that at least what I
yo diría que el por lo menos lo que yo
appreciated I would say more or less
aprecié yo diría que igual más o menos
the same standard of living as here when it comes to
el nivel de vida que que aquí a la hora
buying spending and
de comprar gastar y
so on It is the same as in Disney for
demás Igual igual sea en Disney por
example I bought some popcorn some
ejemplo me compré unas palomitas unas
popcorn They cost me 5 bucks
palomitas Me costaron 5 pavos
eh the entrance if I am not mistaken it is around
eh la entrada si no me equivoco rondan
80 the same as the one in
los 80 igual que el de
Paris it is true those are things that I have not
París es verdad son cosas que no he
mentioned in the
comentado en el
video it is like very quiet no no no it is the
vídeo es como muy silencioso no no no es
same as the one in Paris with its background music it
igual que el de París con su música de
is that it is the same as the one in Paris the one in Paris
fondo es que es igual que el de París el
is better the one in Paris is better
de París es mejor el de París es mejor
the
la
truth is the one in Paris is better let's see if you
verdad el de París es mejor a ver si
have been to the one for 5 for shovels mama already
habéis ido el de 5 por palitas mama ya
but the same as the same as in all the
pero igual que que de igual que en todos
parks
los parques
Max the same as in all the
Max igual que en todos los
eh For example I bought clothes in Hong
eh Por ejemplo me compré ropa en Hong
Kong I have  I was explaining before
Kong lo he estadoa explicando antes en
on telesalseo, let's see. It costs the same, yes,
en telesalseo a ver Cuesta lo mismo si
that my wife bought a sar. It seems to me
que mi mujer compró un sar yo a mí me da
that the economy is more or
la impresión de que la economía más o
less the same, uh, the economy is more or less the same,
menos igual eh la economía más o menos
the expenses and such as here,
igual los gastos y tal igual que
here on this channel, the last video that
aquí en este canal el último vídeo que
was uploaded where the thumbnails and
ha subido que salen las miniaturas y
yuan and Agus appear. Yes, that was the newscast,
yuan y Agus Sí eso ha sido el noticiero
it's that, uh, Inves is busy with the
es que eh inves está liado con con la
series and then the
serie y entonces pues lo está subiendo
other editor is uploading it and maybe the newscast doesn't come out as
el otro editor y a lo mejor no sale tan
quickly as the one in Orlando, it's
rápido el noticiero como el de Orlando
going to cost a fortune. Well, I don't know
se va a un dineral Pues no lo sé el Por
why, I imagine that more than anything because of the
qué me imagino que más que nada por el
move. I don't
traslado no
know, honestly, I don't know, honestly. Let's
No lo sé la verdad no lo sé la verdad A
see if we go to the one in Orlando, not on
ver si vamos a al de Orlando no en
some occasion.
alguna ocasión
No, what happens is that in order for me to
No lo que pasa que para que yo pueda
block, I have to go without the
bloquear tiene que ser que vaya sin los
children, obviously. If I go with children, no, I'm not
niños evidentemente Si voy con niños no
going to record, obviously.
no voy a grabar evidentemente
I think it's very nice, but the most
Me parece muy bonito pero lo más
important thing is the humility that you have,
importante es la humildad que vos tenés
Javi, that's what it's all about, man.
Javi eso es lo que realmente hombre
Thank you very much, Rosa. Thank you very much
Muchas gracias Rosa Muchísimas gracias
for your
por tus
words.
palabras
How about maybe it's there?  where
Cómo que igual si es allá donde se
every man is made has some little
fabrica todo hombre tiene algunas
things it has some little things that
cosillas tiene algunas cosillas que que
are more peculiar because we are
son más peculiares porque estamos
talking about China
hablando de China
but
pero
but but let's see the one in Paris if you have been to
pero pero a ver el de París si habéis
Paris it has the Disneyland Park
ido al de París tiene el Disneyland Park
and the Disney Studio and the Village Well the one
y el Disney Studio y el Village Bueno
in Hong Kong is only the
pues el de Hong Kong es solamente el
Disneyland Park one the entrance and the
Disneyland Park una la entrada ya la
hotels and all that. I didn't go to see it I don't
parte de hoteles y demás no fui a verla
know what it will be like But there was no Village nor
no sé cómo será Pero no había Village ni
was there Disney Studio I mean there was
había Disney Studio o sea solamente
only the theme there was only the Disneyland
tema solo había el tema de Disneyland
Park theme with some little things more than the one
Park con alguna cosilla que otra más que
in Paris but also with many
la de París pero también con muchas
less little things I don't know
cosillas menos no sé por
why they won't forgive you when I was
qué no te lo van a perdonar cuando tenía
5 a year old my parents didn't take me to a
5 a año mis padres no me llevaron a un
Mecano concert and even at 42 I still
concierto de Mecano y aún con 42 se lo
throw it in their face man I will try to make
sigo echando en cara hombre yo intentaré
Leo see it as if it was a
al Leo hacérselo ver como que pasó al
time gone by it was a time gone by you know like it's
tiempo pasó al tiempo sabes como que es
something from the past that we went
algo del del pasado que que fuimos por
there and he was very small or whatever you
allí y él era muy pequeño o lo que sea
know but it's not a place to
sabes pero es que no es un sitio para
take children it's not a trip to
llevar a los niños no es un viaje para
take children but we're not going to
llevar a los niños pero vamos ni de
joke or joke
coñima ni de coñima
not to be unless at some point
a no ser a no ser que en algún momento
we have the power no and and we go in
tengamos el el poderío no y y vayamos en
fir cl like the fir Class not like
fir cl como el fir Class no como el
gref like gref no I mean if it
gref como el gref no O sea así si se
takes 15 hours on a plane I curse myself
hacen 15 horas de avión me cago en la
have you seen gref's video
[__] habéis visto el vídeo de
have you seen the greev video
gref habéis visto el el el vídeo de
firc
firc
you can compensate your children with another
puedes compensar a tus hijos con otro
trip but just a family trip I told
viaje pero solo familiar yo le dije a
Lorena that we should go to Disneyland Paris as soon
Lorena de irnos al Disneyland París tal
as we got here but she said
y como llegásemos aquí pero ella decía
no that she didn't feel like going
que no que no tenía ganas de ir ya a
anywhere imagine if the kid gets lost
parte imagínate se llega a perder el
in China with all the people
chico en China con la de gente que hay
there but it's not that but apart from that no
ahí pero que no es eso sino aparte que
no it's not that it's that it's 15 hour flights
no que no son que son 15 horas de vuelo
one of the flights but then there's another
uno de los vuelos pero luego hay otro
flight that was three no or four I don't
vuelo que era de tres no o de cuatro no
remember how long the other one was no no the
me acuerdo cuánto era el otro no no el
other I think it was 2 and a half almost
otro creo que eran de 2 y media casi
three And then
tres Y luego
from the airport to the sanctuary another 3
el del aeropuerto al santuario otras 3
hour drive to the jungle that we went
horas de coche a la selva esa que fuimos
was 4 hour drive
fueron 4 horas de coche
and let's see if we had gone with the
e a ver que si hubiéramos ido con los
kids Well  we would have adapted but it
niños Pues nos hubiéramos adaptado pero
's not a trip for LL for the children
que no es un viaje para LL a los niños
really
realmente
man it's not a trip for the children
hombre no es un viaje para los niños
Look at me the animals are wild
Mira me me los animales son salvajes el
Leo is not going to respect no no well
Leo no va a respetar no no pues a la
stop the capi don't touch her no no Leo is going to
capí paraa no la toques no no el Leo va
go to the capi stop and he's going to get into a
ir a la capí paraa y se va a montar los
fight and look at the otters that
harto y las fíjate tú las nutrias que
are chasing you every day Leo
están Todo días persiguiéndote el Leo
would grab them by the tail up and
las cogerías de la cola para arriba para
down one day vo One day I'm going to censor the
abajo un día vo Un día voy a censurar la
child's face in a video that I have of the
cara del niño en un vídeo que tengo del
child picking up
niño cogiendo
snakes and I'm going to show it to you it's
serpientes y os lo voy a enseñar es que
because c I had to send it to Fran and he didn't
por c se lo tenía que mandar a Fran y no
send it to him that he asked me but I
se lo ha mandado que me lo pidió pero os
have to one day I'm going to censor his
tengo que le voy a censurar un día la
face to put the video here of the child
cara para poneros aquí el vídeo del niño
picking up the picking snakes and the
cogiendo la cogiendo serpientes y el
child picks up the snake like the one who is
niño coge serpiente como el que está
picking
cogiendo
eh like the one who is picking up one
eh como el que está cogiendo un peluche
of these stuffed animals here Hey there are the crocs
de estos de aquí Oye ahí están las crocs
there are the crocs the the the child who eh
ahí están las crocs el el el niño que eh
loves animals loves animals is crazy
ama los animales ama los animales flipa
but of course it is  very little boy
pero claro es chico muy
exactly Look Maribel has described it
exactamente Mira Maribel la ha descrito
perfectly children don't know how to measure
perfectamente los niños no saben medir
their love for
su cariño por los
animals when the boy
animales cuando el niño
is 15 I will already
tenga 15 años ya lo
take him but the thing is that here there are also
llevo pero es que aquí también hay
animals to see and there are
animales que ver y
places to see animals and
hay hay sitios donde Ver animales y
reserves and a lot of places that
reservas y un montón de sitios que
we
nosotros
go you took croc to Frank no
vamos le llevaste croc a Frank no
Maleficent I took him
Maléfica le llevé
a t-shirt and some socks that I can't
una camiseta y unos calcetines que estoy
wait for him to put on and he hasn't
deseando que se ponga y no se lo ha
put it on yet and I can't wait for him to
puesto todavía y estoy deseando que se
put it on because it will be so cool when he
ponga porque es un puntazo cuando se la
puts it on ilani It's that I don't have any more room here
ponga ilani Es que aquí no me cabe más
In fact I have to do the I have to do the I'll
nada De hecho tengo que hacer el tengo
tell you the
el te lo diré la mini tengo que hacer la
mini I have to do the mini I have to do the mini I have to do
mini tengo que hacer la mini tengo que
the mini I really have to
hacer la mini realmente tengo que
do it
hacerla
Okay I have to do the mini eh
Vale tengo que hacer la mini eh
kids did you bring the crocodile crosses
chavales trajiste las cruz de cocodrilo
Yes yes of course I brought them
Sí sí claro que las traje
look I have them there I have them I was
mira Ahí las tengo ahí los
going to leave them there but but
tengo iba a dejarlas por allí pero pero
the lor took them they are bitten he is
la lor las cogió están mordidas le
missing two he is missing two teeth Because he
faltan dos le faltan dos dientes Porque
tore them out
los arrancó
plexi
plexi
but but look here are the Crosses what
pero pero mira aquí están las Cross queé
art eh wow what a cool thing when I
arte eh [__] qué puntazo cuando las
chrome them  Fran gave them to me, eh, it has been
crome me las dio el Fran eh que ha sido
a very nice experience, man, the truth
una experiencia muy guapa tío la verdad
is that it makes me very nostalgic when I see
es que me da mucha nostalgia Cuando veo
the videos because now, for example,
lo los vídeos porque ahora por ejemplo
eh, now, for example,
eh ahora por ejemplo
Lorena told me, I haven't seen it
me me dijo Lorena yo no lo he visto
yet, I've seen some video
todavía yo he visto algún algún vídeo
that I've seen around here, such as
que me ha salido por aquí tal
grandpa, you can hear yourself breathing, Nachito, that's his thing, that
abuelo se te escucha respirar Nachito es
's his thing, that you can hear it when,
lo suyo es lo suyo que se escuche cuando
no, when you're not breathing, bad thing, apart from that,
no cuando no respire mal asunto aparte
I'm very fond of eh, I have a cold that I ca
que estoy muy aficio eh tengo un cataro
n't see, you have the mark of the
que no veo tienes la marca de la
snake bite, it's a bite,
picadura de la serpiente es un mordisco
Oliver, but no, no, there's no mark, no, I'll
Oliver pero no no no hay marca no Lo
put the video on Twitter. Do you want me to
pondré en Twitter el vídeo queréis que
put it on Twitter? I'll
lo ponga en
put the video on Twitter. Yes, I'm
Twitter lo pongo en Twitter el vídeo sí
not going to put it on Twitter because on
no lo voy a poner en Twitter que en
Twitter there's no censorship.
Twitter no hay censura
Wait, it's that there in the
espérate es que ahí en el vídeo de
YouTube video I say, no, don't put the blood
YouTube digo no no pongáis la sangre
because these people on
porque esta gente en
YouTube, watch the
YouTube a ver el
video, they have teeth, they don't have teeth. Grab it.
vídeo tiene dientes que no tiene dientes
Oh,
cógela Ay
grab it. I'll let it go a little bit more here.
cógela la suelto un poquito más acá
Wait, wait, I'm going to put it on Twitter,
Espera espera lo voy a poner en Twitter
okay?
vale
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Tejala. There, hard, there, hard, a little higher
tejala Ahí fuerte ahí fuerte un poco más
there, damn it's not going to happen.  bite she's not going to
ahí hostias no te va a morder no te va a
bite you Ah she bit me she's
morder Ah me ha mordido me está
biting me Fran
mordiendo Fran
let me go me me biting you she's biting you me [ __ ]
suéltamela me mendo te está mordiendo
look how she bites Look
meendo [__] mira có muerde a Mira otra
again Oh look if she lets me she'll leave her
vez Ay mira si me deja me deja los
teeth on my shirt she's a radiata close close
dientes en la camiseta es una radi
c close close she's not
cierra cierra c cier cier cierra no te
going to bite you she's got no teeth she's a radiata
va a morder no tiene dientes es una radi
a little a
deab un poquito un
little she's not going to bite you she's got no
poquito no te va a morder no tiene
teeth It's okay Now we cover it up
dientes No pasa nada Ahora lo tapamos
with the [ __ ] tattoo It's a sandwich
con el tatuaje de [__] Es un bocadillo
what you
lo que tú
wanted when I see her out dig no
querías cuando la veo fuera dig no
tien Ah it's nothing don't close her
tien Ah no es nada no la
Cristina quiet me no me no What are you
ces Cristina callada yo no yo no Qué
saying what did you say this is a meme this is a
dices qué di esto es de meme esto es de
meme Take it out remember remember editor
meme Sácale acuérdate acordar editor
when she says I no I no that's great that
cuando dice yo no yo no es buenísimo
my god man he made me bleed what
madre mía hombre me ha echo sangre lo
Crisina wanted is a radiata Damn Do
que quería crisina es una radiata [__]
n't shut up a viper Don't take
Que no call una víbora a m No me saque
anything out of me now I have enough internet balls
ya nada que Bastante tengo golas de
damn do you think Seriously not Fran
[__] has creído En serio que no el Fran
all the time Nando to the turbo the
todo el tiempo Nando al turbo el
Cab Turbo no to the Turbo no Fran time
Cab Turbo no al Turbo no el Fran tiempo
mentioning me to half of YouTube I mean I do
mencionándome a medio YouTube o sea yo
n't even know whose names
no sé ni cuos nombres le tenido que
the editor was telling me to remove and today
decía el editor que quite y hoy se me
one slipped in that I didn't want mentioned
coló uno que no quería que mencionara
but I don't even know How many names I
pero yo no sé ni Cuántos nombres le he
had to tell the editor Take this off Take that off
tenido que decir al editor Quítame esto
cut it out Fran you [ __ ]
Quítame lo otro corta Fran cabrón
shut up and he wouldn't stop putting people p
cállate y no paraba de meterme gente p
messing with people he's messed with
meterse con la gente se ha metido con
everything kiki he's messed with everything kiki in
todo kiki se ha metido con todo kiki en
all the brutes that's why I'm checking
todos los brutos por eso estoy revisando
the Brute before uploading it to Twitter I
el Bruto antes de subirlo a Twitter
came there and she was a little
venía ahí y estaba un poco
aggressive she doesn't bite she doesn't bite damn
agresiva no muerde no
that one can bite you 12 times without a
[__] esa te puede morder 12 veces sin
guy son of a [ __ ] what a [ __ ]
tío hij [__] qué cabrona
eh what a [ __ ] Fran is worth it Yes we
eh qué cabrona el Fran se vale Sí lo
uploaded it to Twitter come on come on We
subimos a Twitter venga
uploaded it to Twitter uncensored I'm going
va Lo subimos al Twitter sin censura voy
to
a
put a [ __ ] on it but everyone is
ponerle [__] pero está todo el mundo
talking about seling eh I'm going to see it now I'm going
hablando de lo de seling eh voy ya a
to see it now wait I'm going to
verlo Voy a verlo ya espérate voy a
put this and we'll see it I'm going to put the
poner esto y ya lo vemos Voy a poner el
tweet HM let's see
tweet HM a ver
my Souvenir from
mi Souvenir de
Thailand No that that's
Tailandia No eso eso es una
nonsense I'm going to put the  snake bite
tontería voy a poner la mordedura de
uncensored the bite No no how do I put What do I
censura la mordedura No no cómo pongo
put What do I put What do I put What do I
Qué pongo Qué pongo Qué pongo Qué pongo
put What do I
Qué pongo Qué pongo
put What do I put What do I put I'm
Qué pongo Qué
going to put
pongo voy a poner
Hey my
Eh mi
video my video my
vídeo mi vídeo mi
bite viper bites me I died of a
mordedura víbora muerde me muer de una
snake and also an rtil no no wait no no no no no just kidding just kidding
serpiente y también un rtil no no espera
I faced a viper
me enfrenté a una víbora ataque de
viper attack my first time with a
víbora mi primera vez con una
snake my first time with a
serpiente mi primera vez con una
snake
serpiente
[Music]
[Música]
mm my first time viper attack
mm mi primera vez ataque de vívora sin
uncensored but it's not a viper
censura pero es que no es una vívora
No it's not a
No no es una
viper it's not a viper not
víbora no es una víbora no
a
una
radiata snake bite it's
radiata mordedura de serpiente ya
done Today is the Pon twittero vs Javi
está Hoy es el Pon twittero vs Javi
oliveira Tomorrow I'll put it
oliveira Mañana la pongo
on instagram okay I'll put it on
en en instagram vale os lo pongo en
Twitter on instagram it's that yes there may be
Twitter en instagram es que si puede que
problems not on instagram yes there may be
haya problemas no en instagram sí puede
problems
que haya problemas
not on instagram with the blood Yes there may be a little
no en instagram con la sangre Sí puede
problem
haber problemilla
no calm down if it doesn't have teeth pum
no tranquilo si no tiene dient pum
bite let's see come on I upload the video come on
mordisco a ver venga subo el vídeo venga
Get on, [ __ ],
Súbete cabrón
now Marina, yes, I get them, here
ya yo Marina es que sí las cojo ya aquí
in Seville I also get them where I've
en Sevilla también las cojo en
gotten them. Already several times what Juan
la he cogido Ya varias veces lo de Juan
Luis did, bad game, I go there almost every
Luis mal partida que allí voy casi todos
weekend. Hey, come on, those likes are very good,
semana Oye venga esos like muy bien
Leonia, yes, I
leonia sí me
like them, time went by quickly,
gusta el tiempo pasó rápido
eh. Ah, okay, it says a place that's going to
eh Ah vale que dice lugar que me va a
send me the click with context. Ah, okay, I
mandar el click con contexto Ah vale Yo
was seeing some people's t's around here,
estaba viendo por aquí algunos t de la
but well, I'm seeing it around here on
gente pero bueno lo voy viendo por aquí
Twitter, while we'll
por Twitter de mientras
see, now we'll see the
a ver ahora vemos el
context because here I'm seeing that
contexto porque aquí estoy viendo yo que
everyone is talking about this topic, I
todo el mundo está hablando de este tema
mean, it's like ar from Twitter with
o sea está como que ar de Twitter con
seling, I spoke with delox today. I spoke with
con seling hablé con delox hoy Hablé con
delox this weekend, coming up, I don't know
delox en el fin de semana viene no sé
what day, okay, but I'll meet
qué día vale pero qued haré con
him. Tomorrow is Friday, so I'll meet
él mañana es viernes pues qued haré con
him on Saturday or Sunday, okay, let's
él el sábado o el domingo vale
see, I'll watch the clip first. Look,
e a ver voy a ver el clip primero Mira
Argentinians are good people,
los argentinos son buena gente
Peruvians are good people, Chileans are
los peruanos son buena gente los
good people, I
chilenos son buena gente los mexicanos
can't stand Mexicans. Man,
no soporto Man a
everyone, I'm fed up with you, crazy, [ __ ] annoying,
todos Hasta los [__] loco [__]
you are And how [ __ ] annoying And what
pesados sois Y qué [__] pesados Y qué
disgusting comments  and what a disgusting fandom
asco de comentarios y qué asco de fandom
And what a disgusting whole lot of people What a [ __ ] bore you all are
Y qué asco de todo loco Qué [__] [__]
really [ __ ] what a [ __ ] bore all of you
dais de verdad [__] qué [__] [__]
all that I have a [ __ ] picture of
todos todo que teng un [__] la foto de
Rivers there Rivers my queens [ __ ]
rivers ahí rivers mis reinas [__]
cring all of you Look, Argentinians are
cring todos Mira los argentinos son
good people Peruvians are
buena gente los peruanos son buena gente
good people Chileans are good people Mexicans I ca
chilenos son buena gente los mexicanos
n't stand you all of you I'm going to beat you all up you
no lo soporto os voy a manar a todos me
have me up to my balls Crazy how [ __ ]
tenéis hasta los [__] Loco qué [__]
annoying you are And what a [ __ ] annoying And what disgusting
pesados sois Y qué [__] pesados Y qué
comments and what a disgusting fandom And
asco de comentarios y qué asco de fandom
what disgusting whole lot of people says Delox
Y qué asco de todo loco dice el delox
Selin is not xenophobic but a strategist
selin no es xenófoba sino una estratega
with more than 200 IQ when she
con más 200 de iq cuando se ha dado
realized Alana's physique she made
cuenta del físico de alana ha hecho
these statements to generate
estas declaraciones para generar
controversy And to be disqualified from the
polémica Y ser descalificada de la
evening and avoid being annihilated with a
velada y evitar ser aniquilada de un
punch in front of millions of people is
puñetazo ante millones de personas es
that Alana is in incredible physical shape
que alana está en forma física increíble
Camil ardo a kiss Hey but Camil ardo
Camil ardo un beso Oye pero Camil ardo
Thank you very much friend I think you have
Muchísimas gracias amigo yo creo que has
given away 50% of the  members that
regalado el 50% de los miembros que
we have right now eh which by the way I think
tenemos ahora mismo eh que por cierto
are wrong I have to look at it I have to
creo que están mal tengo que mirarlo
look at it eh Let's see I have to
tengo que mirarlo eh A ver tengo que
look at the topic the topic member to see the
mirar el tema el tema miembro a ver el
video It's to post it's to post
vídeo Está para postear está para
Let's go see topic members
postear Vámonos a ver tema
members of course there it says
miembros claro ahí pone
2847 Camil ardo just gave away another
2847 Camil ardo acaba de regalar otro
five and while you're all
cinco y mientras que le estáis todos
applauding him I look eh the members
aplaudiendo yo miro eh los miembros
How many are there and we're right now at
Cuántos son y estamos ahora mismo en
2896 we can reach 3000 tonight not
2896 podemos llegar a 3000 esta noche no
again calm down Here talking about
otra vez tranquilito Aquí hablando de
gossip and gossip no alana is
chisme y de salseo no alana está
incredible It's
increíble
incredible the truth is she gives you a slap
increíble la verdad te mete una [__]
and she gives you a slap and she throws you
y te mete una [__] y te tira el
live Javi it ​​is said that alana has been
directo Javi se dice que alana lleva
practicing since September yisa and sel it
practicando desde septiembre yisa y sel
's not normal that they don't want to fight now it's
no es normal que no quieran pelear ahora
not that alana has been practicing since
no es que alana lleve practicando desde
September well alana is here look
septiembre bueno alana está aquí mira 26
September 26th here she already knows that she's going to
de septiembre aquí ya lo sabe que va a
be a participant in the evening but the thing is that
ser participante de la velada pero es
alana is always in shape if
que alana ya está siempre en forma si es
I remember that it was already said
que yo me acuerdo que ya se dijo el año
last year when the rumor of the  of ama blit
pasado cuando el rumor de lo de ama blit
when the rumor of who was going to be the one who was
cuando el rumor de quién iba a ser la
going to fight no
que iba a pelear no
and it was already said that Alana well was a
e ya se dijo que alana bueno era una
possibility in fact I knew her I
posibilidad de hecho yo la conocí yo
knew of her existence because of that because
supe de su existencia por eso porque la
people mentioned her to me as the possible
gente me la mencionaba como la posible
newsboy that was going to replace Who was it
voceador que iba a sustituir a Quién era
Who was it that had to
A quién era que tenía que
replace Who was the one that
sustituir Quién fue la que se
fell
cayó el año
last year when we were talking about ama blis do you
pasado que hablábamos de ama blis os
remember that we were talking about ama blis that
acordáis que hablábamos de ama blis que
in the end amama blis has been this year to
al final amama blis ha sido este año a
murán to murán It's true that she left
murán a murán Es verdad que dejó tirado
the subject hanging Yeah okay
el tema Sí vale
then Wait I have a
entonces Espérate que tengo aquí un
little bit of a mess here with the eyelashes
poquillo de lío de pestaña
okay but
vale pero
here the xenophobia is bad selin the
aquí la xenofobia está mal selin los
children who attack you are not all of Mexico I
niños que te atacan no es todo México
even bet that not all of them are
incluso apuesto a que no todos son
Mexicans the harassment is wrong and I understand
mexicanos el acoso está mal y entiendo
her anger But she chose the wrong words
su enojo Pero escogió mal las palabras
if those who attack you have photos of
si los que te atacan tienen fotos del
Mariana or Rivers it doesn't mean that they
Mariana o rivers no significan que ellos
sent it but that they are followers Let's
lo mandaron sino que son seguidores A
see Look, Argentines are good people,
ver Mira los argentinos son buena gente
Peruvians are good people,
los peruanos son buena gente los
Chileans are good people  Mexicans
chilenos son buena gente los mexicanos
no, they can't stand it, one way you all
no no soportan una manera todos me
have me up to my balls Crazy, how [ __ ]
tenéis hasta los [__] Loco qué [__]
annoying you are And how [ __ ] annoying And what disgusting
pesados sois Y qué [__] pesados Y qué
comments and what a disgusting fandom
asco de comentarios y qué asco de fandom
And how disgusting everything is crazy but I understand
Y qué asco de todo loco pero yo entiendo
that this is a
que esto es una
joke, let's see, I understand that this is not
broma a ver yo entiendo que esto no es
serious but it's not for nothing but because I do
en serio pero no es por nada sino porque
n't think she thinks that all
no creo que ella piense que todos los
Mexicans are fans of Mariana or fans of
mexicanos son fans del Mariana ni fan de
River or fans of amama B I mean, she's
River ni fan de amama B O sea está de
joking Look at one thing and I don't know if you have
broma Mira una cosa y no sé si os habéis
noticed I don't, I don't think this is
cuenta Yo no yo no creo que esto sea en
serious, let's see one thing
serio a ver una cosa
ivai
ivai
ivai has put Spaniards against
ivai ha puesto españoles contra
Latin Americans in the
latinoamericanos en los
fights plex against al
combates plex contra al
Mariana plex against Mariana selin
Mariana plex contra el Mariana selin
and
y
niser against ama bz and
niser contra ama bz y
alana
alana
agusín 51 against
agusín 51 contra
carrera virus against
carrera virus contra
celao Javi Which fights did I know, I'm not
celao Javi Cuáles combates te sabía no
going to say it, I'm not going to say it, but I
lo voy a decir no lo voy a decir pero me
knew some, I knew almost all of them, I
sabía algunos me sabía casi todos me
knew almost all of them but I couldn't say it
sabía casi todos pero no podía decirlo
this time, look, some could have
en esta ocasión mira que alguno podría
been a powerful exclusive but I
haber sido una exclusiva potente pero no
couldn't but I knew almost
podía pero me sabía casi
everyone or rather I don't think this comment
todos o sea yo este comentario no creo
is about me the whole of Twitter
que sea conmigo se metió todo Twitter
Spain got involved and I never said that I was disgusted by
España y nunca dije que me daban asco
the Spanish I always said that I was
los españoles siempre dije que me daba
disgusted by Twitter Spain and now messing with an
asco Twitter España y ya meterse con un
entire country over a group of people is wrong
país entero por un grupo de está mal
Although I agree with Selin that
Aunque estoy de acuerdo con selin en que
how [ __ ] disgusting the shitty kids are with the
qué [__] asco los niños de [__] con la
profile picture of Stream
foto de perfil de Stream
F you are against sing for having a
F estás en contra de sing por opinar
different opinion no Dante I'm going to tell you one
diferente no Dante te voy a decir una
thing I didn't want to talk about the subject so quickly
cosa no quería hablar tan rápido del
but I'm going to talk about it now what
tema pero lo voy a hablar ahora a mí lo
seems completely outrageous to me is that
que me parece una completa barbaridad es
this type of message can be given
que se pueda dar ese tipo de mensaje ya
live and that absolutely
en directo y que no pase absolutamente
nothing happens and that there are even people who
nada y que incluso haya gente que lo
applaud it I think that the message
aplauda yo creo que eso el el mensaje
she gave today is clearly
que dio ella el día de hoy claramente es
an incitement to hatred that does divide
una incitación al odio eso sí que divide
communities not like what they
comunidades no como lo que nos echaron
blamed on me, Sprint and ded a
la culpa a mí a Sprint y a ded hace un
couple of weeks ago and apart from all that it does
par de semanas y aparte de todo eso si
seem to me to have
me parece con tintes
xenophobic overtones I don't want to
xenofóbicos Es que no quiero que me
feel bad now about everything that Juan says
parezca mal ahora todo lo que dice el
man but it's just that
tío pero es que vaya
stupid it's not right to say all the
estupidez no está bien decir toda la
people from such country I don't like there's no
gente de tal país me cae mal no hay
way you don't come off as a
manera en la que no quedes como un
racist saying that there's no
racista diciendo eso es que no hay
way it wouldn't even be racism it
manera es que ni siquiera sería racismo
would be xenophobia in any case because it's not
sería xenofobia en todo caso porque no
messing with the
se está metiendo con la
race Okay then Now I see it separately now I
raza Vale pues Ahora lo veo aparte ahora
see it separately then luare but you have what you
lo veo aparte entonces luare pero tienes
have what seling
lo de tienes lo de seling
what you tell me that you put it in
que me dices que me lo pones con
context I don't want it to seem like
contexto Es que no quiero que parezca
everything I gave now to play seems
que todo lo que di ahora jugar me parece
wrong to me but this seems like a
mal pero es que esto me parece una
sovereign gipy dude I mean this doesn't sound like
soberana gipy tío o sea esto no suena a
you guys I want lare to send me
ustedes Es que quiero que lare me mande
what he's telling me that he's going to
el lo que me está diciendo que me va a
send me the context but no this doesn't
mandar el contesto pero no esto no
seem like you guys the typical [ __ ] what
parece ustedes la típica gilipo que
can we say
podemos decir
here is that it doesn't seem to me that he's
aquí es que no me parece que sea en
serious Look, Argentines are good
serio Mira los argentinos son buena
people, Peruvians are good people,
gente los peruanos son buena gente los
Chileans are good people, Mexicans
chilenos son buena gente los mexicanos
no, I can't stand you, I'm going to kick you all, you've got me
no no soporto os voy manar a todos me
up to my balls Crazy, how [ __ ]
tenéis hasta los [__] Loco qué [__]
annoying you are And how [ __ ] annoying And what disgusting
pesados sois Y qué [__] pesados Y qué
comments and what disgusting fandom
asco de comentarios y qué asco de fandom
And how disgusting everything is crazy but if this
Y qué asco de todo loco pero si esto lo
I can tell you guys any day
puedo decir yo a ustedes cualquier día
that how [ __ ] disgusting are the people who follow me
que qué [__] asco de gente que me sigue
that if you're sick I don't know
que si estáis malitos no sé
what what the [ __ ] is a pain in the ass you're really [ __ ] kidding
qué qué [__] [__] dais de verdad [__]
what the [ __ ] are you all all that I have
qué [__] [__] aar todos todos que teng
if he's laughing
si se está riendo
uncle maderita vaner a [ __ ] picture of
tío maderita vaner un [__] la foto de
rivers there rivers Yari my queens you give
rivers ahí rivers Yari mis reinas dais
[ __ ] cringe I'm going to beat everyone Look,
[__] cringe voy a ganar a todos Mira los
Argentinians are good
argentinos son buena
people it just doesn't seem like it to me man, I mean
gente es que no me parece tío o sea
man if the comment is serious then of course
hombre si el comentario es en serio pues
obviously Yes it is xenophobia
claro evidentemente Sí es xenofobia
Of course you were saying it with the Argentinians he
Claro tú lo decías con los argentinos
says ladies that this is not serious
dice ladyes que esto no es en serio
man but if he's laughing man I don't
hombre pero si se está riendo tío no
understand how you justify that but if it is that he would
entiendo cómo justificas eso pero si es
n't justify it if he was
que no lo justificaría si lo estuviera
saying it seriously but the thing is that I
diciendo en serio pero es que yo esto lo
understand this as a joke let's see what
entiendo como una broma a ver qué es lo
Selin said let's see the likes that you're
selin a ver los likes que me estáis
telling me to look at the likes because I don't
diciendo que mire los likes es que no lo
understand it in any other way
entiendo de otra forma
eh Let's see the
eh A ver los
lik
lik
you are some [ __ ] lunatics he
sois unos energúmenos del carallo
literally said pure factors that it
literalmente ha dicho puros factores que
pisses you off to say because you are so  egomaniacs who
os jode decir porque sois tan ególatras
thinks it's normal to have
que os pensáis que es normal tener a
8 year olds with your
niños de 8 años con vuestras fotos de
profile pictures eating ass in everything you
perfil comiendo el culo en todo lo que
do honestly I don't care if I sound s
hacéis honestamente Me da igual sonar s
but that seling is my favorite streamer
pero que seling es mi streamer favorita
participate in the evening it fills me with
participe en la velada me llena de
pride this has to end I'm
orgullo esto tiene que acabar Estoy
sick of Mexican hate I'm sick of the
harto del odio mexicano Estoy harto del
hate of the Spanish Daniel Thank you very much
odio de los españoles Daniel Muchas
welcome let's start hating
bienvenido empecemos a odiar a los
Peruvians let's see man this is a joke man I
peruanos a ver tío esto es broma tío
think the D put
creo que el D puso
something I swear I saw something on the
algo juraría que vi algo en la cuenta
DT
del D
T account
T
then he put Ari and Rivers out of nowhere to
luego metía a Ari y rivers de la nada a
the dick but will it be all or more some He
la [__] pero serán todos o n más alguno
went too far Okay I'm going for my
Se pasó de [__] Bueno me voy por mi
banana Wait wait we have we have
banana Espera espera que tenemos que
the context
tenemos el contexto
wait it's being processed man
espera se está procesando tío
no to this day it's better not to
no a a día de hoy mejor no
discriminate positions to hate that it is to
discriminar puestos al hate que sea a
everyone I don't hate man I don't hate let's see
todos no me carga tío No me carga a ver
the trending selling trends I knew it
los trending selling tendencias lo sabía
man I
tío lo
knew it I need you to chocas and sel
sabía Necesito que chocas y sel me
explain something to me in Spain this is having
expliquen algo en España esto es tener
education let's
educación a
see but you're not going to beat him I'm
ver pero no le vas a ganar Lo
sorry I'm telling you no Brother I'm telling
siento Ya te digo yo que no Brother ya
you  I don't I
te digo yo que no Yo
trust It's a joke it's [ __ ] dude
confío Es una broma es una chorrada tío
really Hey what's going on here today
de verdad Oye qué pasa hoy aquí en
seriously
serio
Give me a
Dame un
second [ __ ] dude I have WhatsApp
segundito [__] ch tengo el WhatsApp
full of stuff dude
lleno de cosas
okay I
loco vale Ya
'm there that's it
estoy ya está
Sorry Are you scared of Lana la Rana
Perdón Le tienes miedo a lana la rana
Alex if I was scared of Lana la Rana
Alex si tuviese miedo a la lana la rana
when they told me The Combat I would have
cuando me dijeron El Combate le hubiese
said I don't want to participate against Lana
dicho I no quiero participar contra lana
la Rana change her and instead I said
la rana cámbiamela y en cambio he dicho
yes So if fear is facing
que sí Entonces si miedo es enfrentarme
her I don't know what the [ __ ] you're saying it's because I
a ella no sé qué [__] estáis diciendo es
'm really [ __ ] boring really scared I
que soy muy [__] [__] de verdad miedo
mean well I'm not facing her
Es decir pues yo no me enfrento a ella
put me against another one because it's been a long time
ponme a otra porque es que hace mucho
Jim that's not being afraid
Jim eso eso no es tener miedo
facing Johnny saser against her is not being
enfrentarte Johnny saser contra ella no
afraid let's see if they can locate you Let's see if
es tener miedo a ver si os ubic a ver si
I can [ __ ] locate you dude What a pain let's
os [__] ubic loco Qué [__] a
see let's see
ver a
I'm going to go with my countrywoman in this fight
yo yo en este combate voy con mi
okay I know that she's going to get the
paisana vale que yo sé que va a sacar el
neighborhood I know that Celin is going to take it and she's going to
barrio Yo sé que celin va a [__] y va a
get the neighborhood she's not going to care how
sacar el barrio le va a dar igual lo
big the other one is Okay and with
grande que sea la otra Vale y y con
Naster who's a friend okay And me  I really like
naster que es colega vale Y a mí me cae
naster but the thing is that they are going to give him the one from the
naster pero es que que le van a dar la
tiger he doesn't even quote that they are going to give them
del tigre ni cotiza que les van a dar
the doas from the
las doas del
tiger he is going to give him the
tigre le va Le va a dar a del tigre la
money and the sister of the and the sister
lana y la y la hermana del y la hermana
of
de la
Ari the Ari the Ari and ama I don't know if they are
Ari la Ari la Ari y ama no sé si son
daughters or granddaughters of boceadores they are
hijas o nietas de boceadores
not going to give them they are going to give them the
no les van a dar les van a dar la del
peach he said it out of
melocotón lo dijo por
spite selin and nter have more neighborhood
ardida selin y nter tienen más barrio
than daddy's daughters dal alana and ama
que las hijas de papá dal alana y ama
that they are flirts they are going to
que son coquetes van
give him the one from the tiger they are
a van a darle la del
going to give him the one from the tiger the other
tigre van a darle la del tigre las otras
two are they really always from the
dos de verdad es que son siempre de lo
chat are they really always the same from the
chat de verdad es que son siempre lo
same place I mean really I have
mismo del mismo sitio o sea de verdad yo
n't seen any person from Peru
no he visto a ninguna persona de Perú
tell me anything to any person from
decirme que nada a ninguna persona de
Argentina tell me anything they are always from the same
Argentina decirme nada son siempre del
place I mean really I don't care
mismo sitio todos o sea de verdad es que
what you say I don't know why they
me da igual lo que digáis no sé por qué
are so annoying the same ones as always it's
son muy pesados los mismos de siempre es
been 4 days now with all
que llevo así ya 4 días con todos
messages full of people from
mensajes llenos de gente de fandoms de
shitty fandoms with photos of the same ones as
[__] con la fotos de los mismos de
always and everything  balls already and it's been
siempre y est tod los [__] ya y llevo
4 days Eh And I don't know how this is going to end
4 días Eh Y yo no sé cómo va a acabar
eh Because I don't know how to control myself
esto eh Porque me yo no me sé controlar
eh you know it's the same old thing the
eh sabes que es lo mismo de siempre lo
same old thing I have my doubts about one thing eh
mismo yo tengo mis dudas de una cosa eh
taking into account of course is that
teniendo en cuenta claro es que
eh taking into account that it's been 4
eh teniendo en cuenta que lleva 4
days and taking into account that Selin
días y teniendo en cuenta que selin de
suddenly you remember the strike on Uncle
repente os acordáis de del strike al tío
Sur he gave a strike to Uncle Sur
Sur le puso un strike al tío Sur
man you can't be more chill than
tío que no se puede ser más chill que el
Uncle Sur okay because he commented I don't know what I
tío Sur vale porque comentó no sé qué O
mean I don't know if Selin is going to handle
sea yo no sé si si selin va a gestionar
well the exposure that the evening gives you
bien la exposición que te da la velada
eh As always all the time
eh Como de siempre todo el rato por
everywhere all the time if I was
todos lados todo el rato si tuviese
scared chat if I was scared I wouldn't have
miedo chat si tuviese miedo no hubiese
accepted the fight I'm
no hubiese aceptado el combate eso soy
aware of that or it doesn't give me anything to think about I mean if I was
consciente o no da para pensar O sea si
scared I wouldn't have accepted the
tuviese miedo no hubiese aceptado el
[ __ ] fight I wouldn't have lied to me
putísimo combate no me hubiese mentido
about this you understand I would have said
en esto lo entendéis hubiese dicho que
no please stop being a pain in the ass
no por favor dej de dar por culo
my god what a [ __ ] pain
madre mía qué [__] [__] de
really a pain in the ass of people
verdad [__] de gente
dude Chose is tired even of the
loco el choca está cansado hasta de los
fandom it's normal that Chose is being
fandom normal es que a choca lo llevan
insulted with  the photo of el cha is not
insultando con la foto del el cha ni
even loaded and he is already insulting
siquiera está laada y ya está insultando
people with the photo of Mariana for those of us who do
gente con la foto del Mariana por los
not understand much about boxing
que no entendemos mucho de boxeo nos
could you explain to us haa about the 2s versus 2s if you
podías explicar haa del 2s versus 2s si
would have to carry Anisa In case he
tendrías que carrear anisa En caso que
falls by K or if even if it is six
caiga por K o si aunque sean seis
rounds it is only the first three if
asaltos son solo los tres primeros si
he wins them How do you alternate in the
los ganá Cómo os vais alternando en las
fights, I mean, he crashes he can't even do the
peleas o sea el chocas ni siqua hacer
whole fight and he already has ag people fandom
toda la pelea y ya tiene ag gente fandom
with the fo for not answering the people
con la fo por no le contesta a la gente
who are sending him a visa Javi did you see
que le está mandando un visum Javi viste
what Agustín insinuated about Ari yes
lo que insinuó Agustín sobre Ari sí
Dylan and I more or less know what he is
Dylan y más o menos sé a lo que se
referring to but come on it is clear okay what he
referirá pero vamos está clarinete vale
is referring to basically what he is saying is that Agustín, who is a
está diciendo es que Agustín que es
friend of gref, knows more details than what is
amigo de gref sabe más datos de los que
publicly known Tito really people
públicamente Tito de verdad gente por
please do Look, I understand chat with a
favor hac Mira yo entiendo chat cone una
streamer a lot okay I understand To me,
streamer mucho vale yo entiendo A mí
streamers that I really like, please
streamers que me gustan mucho por favor
do not put their profile pictures
no os pongáis su fotito de perfil por
please it is very cringeworthy  really they
favor da muchísimo cringe de verdad que
are fabric The open secret no but there are
son telas El Secreto a voces no pero hay
more things that noy yes but there is more
más cosas queo noy sí pero hay más tela
sailor fabric there are things that are
marinera hay cosas que son tela
sailor fabric do you put your [ __ ]
marinera hagáis poneros vuestra [__]
photo and then if you want you put a tweet
foto y luego ya si queréis ponéis tweet
encouraging your favorite star Well
animando a vuestro stre favorito Pues de
really why do you have to put the
verdad por qué os tenéis que poner la
profile picture you really don't know
fotito de perfil de verdad no sabéis
how it looks it looks from the outside it looks
cómo se queda queda desde fuera queda
ridiculous seriously ridiculous I mean I
ridículo en serio ridículo o sea yo
understand that you like Look you may
entiendo que te guste Mira te puede
like me Juan you may like
gustar yo Juan te puede gustar el
Mariana you may like Rivers you may like
Mariana te puede gustar rivers te puede
everyone but having the Fito
gustar todo el mundo pero tener la Fito
profile picture with little hearts
de perfil con corazoncitos
What does it
Qué
matter what does it matter to have the
importa qué importa tener la foto de
profile picture of whoever you want there are people who do
perfil de quien tú quieras hay gente que
n't want to have their own photo on
no quiere tener su propia foto en redes
social networks and maybe they only have Twitter
sociales y a lo mejor tiene Twitter
to follow the person they
solamente para para seguir a la persona
follow and little else and they put the
que sigue y poco más y se pone la foto
profile picture and that's it there are people with many
de perfil y punto hay gente con muchas
photos of me eh But there are ladies eh There are
fotos mías eh Pero hay señoras eh Hay
ladies of honor with photos of me
señoras de la señoría con fotos mías
because they have Twitter created just
porque tienen el Twitter creado nada más
to follow my things and and they have my
que para seguir mis cosas y y tien mis
photos put as their profile and that's it because they like me
fotos puestas de perfil y punto porque
me and he doesn't want to put his
le gusto yo y no quiere poner su
photo and those who have the photo of
foto y los que tienen la foto de
Cristiano Ronaldo
Cristiano Ronaldo
exactly saving the distances but it is like
exactamente salvando las distancias pero
that [ __ ] it's that I don't know how I don't know I don't
es que es así [__] es que yo no sé cómo
know when also no no no it's
no sé no sé cuando sa también el no no
not because you are not too much
no es porque no es eres demasiado fan no
of a fan there's nothing
tiene nada de
wrong with the ladies are your
malo las señoras son tu
Target but it's not that nothing happens
Target pero es que no es que no pasa
surely there are people who have
nada seguramente hay gente que tenga la
her photo problem when you are me I know
ella problema cuando tú eres yo que sé
a yillo Juan or a Mariana or a rivers
un yillo Juan o un Mariana o un rivers
You have so many people You have so many so
Tienes tantísima gente Tienes tantísima
many people that you can't control
tantísima gente que no puedes controlar
someone putting your profile picture
que alguien se ponga tu foto de perfil
it's impossible or rather because that's what
es imposible o sea porque a ellos lo que
they like No, he doesn't have it chat, I mean he does
le gusta es eso No no la tiene chat o
n't have it I mean you I am
sea no la tiene O sea tú Yo soy el
Mariana okay for example it's my fault that
Mariana vale por ejemplo tengo culpa de
a child puts his profile picture no
que un niño se ponga en foto perfil no
nothing and Neither does anything happen The
nada y Tampoco tampoco pasa nada El
problem is that I mean dude there's no
problema es que o sea tío no hay ningún
problem with putting
problema en que te ponga la foto perfil
your streamer's profile picture The problem is that all
de tu streamer El problema es que todos
those who put their streamer's picture
los que se ponen la foto de su streamer
are toxic I mean look at their Twitter and their
son tóxicos o sea mira su Twitter y su
Twitter is based on seeing what
Twitter se basa en ver lo que hace es
that streamer does every day at all
ese streamer todos los días a todas
hours Or  be that seems toxic to me
horas O sea a mí eso me parece tóxico
be but it's that it's not like that it's just that
sea pero es que es que no es así es que
look at me from what I've noticed okay
mira yo por lo que yo he percatado vale
from some people this
de alguna gente esto
is let's see a little exaggerated and little more I
es a ver un poco exagerada y poco más
don't think it's a big deal eh like
tampoco me parece la gran cosa eh o sea
a little exaggerated And such But well I do
un poco exagerada Y tal Pero bueno
n't see it as a super
tampoco lo veo para una super
funa okay Soul says Who is this
funa vale Soul dice Quién es esta
filthy woman who calls herself selling and
mugrosa que se hace llamar selling y por
why aren't we taking her down yet
qué aún no le estamos dando de baja no
we're not taking her down her Twitch channel
le estamos dando de baja su canal de
you know it you know very well they're going to
tú lo sabes lo sabes de sobra te van a
break your mother they're going to blow you up no matter what
partir la madre te van a reventar te
Alano touches you, ama they're going to kill you
toque alano te toque ama te van a matar
my daughter They're going to turn your head at
hija mía Te van a voltear la cabeza a
gr it's that I wouldn't be so stupid I wouldn't be there he's
gr es que yo no estaría tan huevudo no
right they're going to give him the
estaría ahí tiene razón le van a dar la
tiger let's
del tigre
see what he says Ali I like them
a ver qué dice Ali me caen muy bien
both a lot I like Ari everyone likes him
ellas dos me caen Ari le cae bien todo
now or rather yesterday in the
el mundo ahora o sea ayer en el clip de
Agustín 51 clip I like him a lot I like Agustín I like him
Agustín 51 me cae muy bien Agustín me
on many occasions he's
cae bien me cae bien en muchas ocasion
been stupid but I like him dude this false
ha sido tonto pero me cae bien tío esta
morality or this falsehood of
falsa moralidad o esta falsedad de de
having to  to throw at someone or to
tener que para tirarle a alguien o para
say something about someone no Look I'm going to
decir algo de alguien no Mira te voy a
put you down okay eh who do I tell
poner verde vale eh quién te digo yo a
you Ricky you're a new con but I like you
ti Ricky eres un con nuevo pero me caes
Let's see man if you like her you like her
bien Vamos ver tío si te cae bien te cae
and all that nobody is
bien y tal nadie te lo está
asking you nobody likes me windy I
preguntando nadie me cae bien windy o
mean I don't understand this lie I like them a lot I like them
sea que no entiendo esta falsedad me
both
caen muy bien Ellas dos me caen
extremely well I like her
exageradamente bien me gusta
extremely well exaggeratedly let's say the
exageradamente bien exageradamente vamos
best people I've ever met
las mejores personas que he conocido las
both in my
dos en la
life I know this link about the
vida yo que conozco a es link lo de las
Twitter accounts that I was going to tell you
cuentas de Twitter que os iba a decir
that in the end I didn't tell you it's not that
que al final no os lo he dicho no es que
the person who is
se pegue todo el día la persona que está
on that Twitter account watches their
en esa cuenta de Twitter vigilando a su
streamer all day long it's that maybe they only
streamer es que a lo mejor solamente
have the Twitter account to follow
tiene la cuenta de Twitter para seguir
the streamer And then during the day they're
al streamer Y entonces por el día pues
doing other things that they're not
está haciendo otras cosas que no te está
telling you or maybe they watch other movies
contando o a lo mejor ve otras películas
and don't tell you or series or whatever
y no te la cuenta o series o lo que sea
but they only have Twitter for the
pero solamente tiene el Twitter para el
streamer Let's see not that you know her and I don't
streamer A ver no que la conozcas y no
know who she is for many many many
sé quién es desde hace muchos muchos
years she was also like one of the
muchos años también fue como de las
first to be on
primeras en estar en en
Twitch I've
Twitch
never spoken to her  I think but I
nunca he hablado con ella creo pero
also love watching her clips they make me
también me encanta ver sus clips me dan
laugh a lot if you haven't talked to her if
mucha risa si no has hablado con ella si
not if you haven't exchanged a word with her
no si no te has cruzado palabra con ella
How are you going to like her excessively I
Cómo te va a caer exageradamente
like her excessively
bien Me cae exageradamente bien clip de
Naster's clip let's see Naster's clip
naster a ver clip de
two against one I lost the Bot the
dos contra uno he perdido la Bot en el
moment she came at me she
momento en el que me ha venido me ha
threw Herald from behind me And they gave me
tirado heraldo por detrás Y me han diado
dude Shut up [ __ ] But if before that
tío Cállate la [__] Pero si antes ya de
the dick
ahí la [__]
dude what game have you seen he was
tío qué partida has visto tú el estaba
in [ __ ] you're
en [__] eres
mu listen to me I'm going to tell you once
mu escúchame te lo voy a decir una vez
more You're a [ __ ] piece of [ __ ] You're a
nada más Eres un [__] [__] Eres un
[ __ ] piece of [ __ ] You're a [ __ ] piece of [ __ ] why
[__] [__] Eres un [__] [__] por me
are you blaming me You're a [ __ ] piece of [ __ ] it
estás culpando a m Eres un [__] [__]
's that you don't even listen to what I
es que ni siquiera escuchas lo que te
'm
estoy
telling you dude I was about to go
diciendo tío estaba a punto de subir a
platinum dude and it has to [ __ ] me
platino tío y me tiene que [__] la
up that he doesn't respect me at all he doesn't
vida que no me respeta nada no me
respect me at all don't get out of here because I don't
respeta nada que no vete de aquí que no
even want to see your
te quiero ni ver la
face you can't like a person
cara no te puede caer bien una persona
for the four clicks that are circulating out
por los cuatro clics que van rulando por
there I mean these clicks are understood by the
ahí o sea estos clics los entienden las
people who follow their Lore
personas que siguen el Lore de ellos
okay or
vale o sea esto yo porque sé que ellos
be this me because I know that they insult each other in the Streams and they start to exaggerate and fight and yell at each other and stuff like that, okay, whatever. But anyone who sees this clip and doesn't know their lor and doesn't understand their environment, no, and their thing in the live shows. Well, they don't get
rollo en los directos No pues no pilla
this, cl, but you can't
esto cl pero no te puede caer
really like a person seeing
exageradamente bien una persona viendo
their C, how they are both really rare, they
su C de que cómo son bien reras las dos
are if Juan had continued
ellas son si Juan me hubiera seguido
allowing me LoL they would be my spirit
permitiendo LoL ellas serían mi espíritu
animal friends, I mean, when I was a
animal amigos o sea yo cuando era una
lolera, I like them a lot. I really like them both. I
lolera me caen muy bien Ellas dos me
like them who else has said something out
gusta quién más ha dicho algo por
there they
ahí
are reporting
están denunciando el
Twitch. This chick got up from her
Twitch Esta tía hoy se ha levantado de
nap today, she opened a live show and
la siesta ha abierto directo y ha
decided to reincarnate herself as the s champion.
decidido reencarnarse en el s campeador
I'm going to uncover a melon that I don't know if
voy a destapar un melón que no sé por
any Spanish streamer has
ningún streamer español se ha dado
noticed or talked about this, but
cuenta o ha hablado de esto pero
September, its independence for Mexico
septiembre su independencia para México
against Spain are gems after gems, that
contra España son joyitas tras joyitas
and that it is pure and hard xenophobia. I
que eso y que es full xenofobia pura y
don't think so,
No creo
honor to Selin and her holy balls, she
no honor a selin y a sus santos [__]
has those of color, those of
tiene a los de color a los del color
humble color throwing  foaming at the
humilde echando espuma por la
mouth
boca
this is a photo not a video let's
esto es una foto no es un vídeo
see I
a ver yo
sincerely would like to think that it's an
sinceramente quisiera pensar que es una
exaggeration the click that he didn't
exageración el click que no lo ha dicho
literally mean it eh I would like to think
literalmente en serio eh Quisiera pensar
that okay dude okay
eso vale tío vale
dude you're making me feel like
tío estás haciendo sentir como una
[ __ ] stop blaming me for everything
[__] deja de echarme la culpa de todo
dude okay dude it's moving me Ari
tío vale tío me está moviendo Ari
Gameplay two points I
Gameplay dos puntos me caen
really like them when I see their
exageradamente bien cuando veo sus
clips I really like them when I
clips me caen exageradamente bien cuando
see their clips let's see La Movida this
veo sus clips a ver La Movida esta
La Movida this of the breakup between
de La Movida esta de la ruptura entre
Abi and carch is giving a lot to talk about
Abi y carch está dando mucho que hablar
on Twitter there are people drawing their own
en Twitter hay gente sacando sus propias
conclusions Abi left carche well
conclusiones Abi dejó a carche bueno
wait first I'm going to see the clip is that we
espera primero voy a ver el clip es que
really should see the
realmente tendríamos que ver la la
breakup no that we didn't see it let's see the
ruptura no que no la vimos a ver la
breakup was this cares confirms the end
ruptura fue esta cares confirma el fin
of her relationship with cares confirms the end
de su relación con cares confirma el fin
of her relationship with Abi it had been
de su relación con Abi se venía
speculated that they had separated and
especulando que se habían separado y
indeed they had been separated for some time
efectivamente llevaban un tiempo
and all this coincides with the fact
separados y todo esto coincide además
that she will be at the evening her Prime will return
con que estará en la velada volverá su
and Abi what do you think of your
Prime y Abi qué piensas de tu
participation in the evening
participación en la velada
eh
eh
guys eh that this is already there have been many
chavales eh que esto ya ya hay muchas
questions lately and so on and yesterday I
preguntas últimamente y demás y ayer lo
spoke about it with  her at night and this
lo hablé con ella por la noche y esta
morning and and we've already spoken to her and everything's
mañana y y le hemos hablado ya y todo
fine okay but April and I have
bien vale pero abril y yo hace ya tres
n't been together for three weeks okay we
semanas que no estamos juntos vale lo
broke up a week before the move
dejamos a una semana de la de la mudanza
and and that's it because I wish her the best and and the
y y ya está que la deseo lo mejor y y
end so she stops asking and everything
fin para que deje de preguntar y demás
okay I'm not going to make a
vale no voy a hacer ni ningún
show or bring it up again
espectáculo ni lo voy a volver a sacar
or anything because it's not a topic that I want to
ni nada porque no es un tema que quiera
do right now or content
hacer ahora mismo ni ni contenido de
or anything like that and I don't want it to
ello ni ni nada de eso ni tampoco quiero
drag on okay But that you guys
que se alargue vale Pero eso que que ya
who are here know, those of you who
lo sepáis los que estáis aquí los que
are in my community okay Abi also
sois de mi comunidad vale Abi también lo
said it live she explained it a little more and
dijo en directo se explay un poco más e
even gave some reasons and through
incluso dio alguna razón y mediante
Instagram she also left a message
Instagram también dejó un mensaje
confirming the breakup it's true like
confirmando la ruptura es verdad como
Abi has explained it more he he has
que Abi se ha explayado más él él lo ha
he has treated it very lightly he has
él lo ha tratado muy de puntilla él lo
treated it very lightly and and she has like
ha tratado muy de puntillas y y ella
Play or more I don't know if it's because of
como que ha Play o más no sé si es por
something in particular or simply part of
algo en concreto o simplemente parte de
the personality of each one
la personalidad de cada uno
eh I remember that at the time she was the one who was
eh me acuerdo que en su día ella era la
most eager to tell it do you
que tenía como más ganas de contarlo os
remember but of course at the time  I
acordáis pero claro en su día eso yo lo
link that to the fact that she was more eager to
vincul a que ella tenía más ganas de
tell it Because for her in terms of numbers she
contarlo Porque a ella a nivel números
was the one who benefited from it being known
era la que le venía bien que se supiera
ex being public because she exploded in fact she
ex siera público porque explotó de hecho
exploded deo
explotó deo
exploded like crazy no when when they
explotó que te cagas no cuando cuando lo
made it public and then I link the
hicieron público y entonces yo vincul el
issue of numbers to the fact that she was so
tema números a que ella tuviera tantas
eager to express it no and now the fact
ganas de expresarlo no y ahora el hecho
that she expands more than him because he
de que ella se explaye más que él porque
is like that he is
é lo como que lo él es
more let's say jealous of his privacy no he he
más digamos celoso de su intimidad no el
he tiptoes around things
él él pasa de puntilla sobre las cosas
of intimacy and so on he
de la intimidad y demás el pasa de
tiptoes no and at the same time to make it
puntillas no y a la vez que para hacerlo
public he was not the one who existed the most no
público no fue é el que más existió no
the publication in fact she made it and the one who
la publicación de hecho la hace ella y
was carrying and the one who had been
el que llevaba y la que llevaba tiempo
spouting thorns for a long time that they were together was
sando puas de que estaban juntos era
her here in the breakup it's the same
ella aquí en la ruptura es lo mismo
guys that there are already several questions on the
chavales que ya van varias preguntas del
subject that I make clear here but without
tema que lo dejo claro aquí pero sin
creating content or anything in the middle of the
crear contenido ni nada en mitad del
live a 3 second click that we are no longer we
directo un click de 3 segundos que ya no
broke up three weeks ago I
estamos lo dejamos hace tres semanas le
wish her the best and see you later okay but
deseo lo mejor y hasta luego vale pero
at most she does not make a publication
ella como más no hace una publicación
here Rosita with  with this very well
aquí Rosita con con este texto muy bien
written text no
escrito no
eh Carlos and I have left it you know
eh Carlos y yo lo hemos dejado ya sabéis
that well he has been very bad
que pues él ha estado muy mal
lately and we decided that it was better for him to
últimamente y decidimos que era mejor
focus on his the sets the sets
que se centrase en su los set los setas
are not the same no I mean they have changed
no son los mismos no O sea han cambiado
the sets
los set los
both Of course at the moment at the moment
dos Claro en el momento en el momento
that at the moment that both change the
que en el momento que ambos cambian el
Setup there I think that for their
Setup ahí yo creo que para sus
followers no
seguidores no Qué fue lo último que
What was the last thing we commented on about any of them it seems to me that before I left it seems to me that before I left Oh the last one you know that the last newscast was shot down man they gave me a strike in the last newscast with
un strike en el último noticiero con
60,000 views
60.000 visitas
man they gave me a strike in the last
tío me pusieron un strike en el último
newscast and I think that there was something in it about
noticiero y creo que ahí salía algo de
Abi they were going to
Abi
move in together But they broke up
se iban a mudar juntos Pero terminaron
a week before
una semana antes de
moving and Abi moved alone with her friend
mudarse y se mudó solo Abi con su amiga
Ah I mean people weren't surprised
Ah o sea que la gente no no se extrañó
not by the move man What a shame that they
no de la mudanza tío Qué pena que me
shot down the last newscast eh Because of a
tumbaron el último noticiero eh Por un
gif that
gif que metió
luare put in that you couldn't see anything but well
luare que no se veía nada pero bueno
ytube understood it as
ytube lo entendió como
sexual like it was  to get you
sexual como que era para ponerte
horny and it was like what we're
cachondo y era como lo que estamos
explaining is news churra I'm
explicando es una noticia churra tengo
scared I'm scared Who will be the next
miedo tengo miedo Quién será el próxima
streamer victim of Gabi what career will she
streamer víctima de Gabi qué carrera
ruin
arruinará
now it's not about the career that she
ahora no se trata de la carrera que
ruins it's about the fact that she still wants to ruin
arruine se trata de que todavía al
Carche I think that she's going to want to
carche yo creo que que lo va a querer
funar it eh really hard at some point or
funar eh bien fuerte en algún momento o
rather the Yesterday when I saw
sea la Ayer cuando cuando vi el mensaje
her message on Twitter I said Ah Well look I
de ella en Twitter dije Ah Bueno mira la
see good vibes but now watching the
veo buen rollo pero ahora viendo los
videos I don't see them eh I don't see that they
vídeos no les veo yo eh No lo veo yo que
broke up with so much good vibes eh
hayan terminado con tanto buen rollo eh
Yesterday when I saw her message This one
Ayer cuando vi el mensaje de ella Este
that we read where Uncle Shur and others that we
que leímos donde el tío shur y demás que
commented on it very superficially
lo comentamos así como muy por encima
without seeing the clips the truth is I don't know
sin ver los clips la verdad no sé por
why I didn't see the clips the truth is that
qué no vi los clips la verdad es que
yesterday I was tired When I did the
ayer estaba cansad Cuando hice el
live and such I didn't feel like
directo y tal no tenía muchas ganas de
elaborating but now watching the videos I
explayarme pero ahora viendo los vídeos
don't see it I do
no le veo yo
n't see it the great
no le veo yo la una gran
cordiality I don't notice a good
cordialidad no noto yo aquí un buen
vibe here situation and that each one went
rollo situación y que cada uno fuese por
their own way eh that doesn't mean that now
su lado eh eso no quiere decir que ahora
we're going to kill each other it doesn't mean that now we're
nos vayamos a matar no quiere decir que
going to  start taking out clips of It's that
ahora vayamos a empezar a sacar clips de
he is that he is that she is that
Es que él es que él es que ella es que
such Not at all, I love Carlos
tal Para nada yo a Carlos lo quiero
very much and I will always love him, he is a
mucho y lo voy a querer siempre es
very special person to me, he has been
persona muy especial para mí lo ha sido
during these two years of relationship this
durante estos dos años de relación esta
relationship has been super beautiful H I'm going
relación ha sido superbonita H Me la voy
to keep it until the day I die
a guardar hasta el día que me muera
em So out of respect for what it has been
em Entonces por respeto a lo que ha sido
Eh well I hope that you can understand it,
Eh pues espero que podáis entenderlo
you can respect it, in the end there were a lot of
podáis respetarlo al final había mucha
people who hated him, there were a lot of
gente que lo odiaba a él había muchísima
people who hated me
gente que me diaba a mí
eh We have already separated I hope that you
eh Ya nos hemos separado Espero que esto
take this to focus on who
os lo toméis para centrar en quien
you love and not to throw heat at the other
queréis y no para tirarle heate al otro
I hope that you take it eh With all the
Espero que os Lo toméis eh Con todo el
possible respect in the end I
respeto posible al final yo esto lo
have to tell this because we have been a
tengo que contar porque hemos sido una
public couple it was my personal life but
pareja pública era mi vida personal pero
eh I made it public and as I told the
eh la hice pública y como conté el
beginning I have to tell the end
comienzo tengo que contar el final
Oh and nothing
Ah y nada
mm I hope Just that it goes superb for him, I am
mm espero Solo que le vaya superb estoy
super proud of him, I know that it will go
super orgullosa de él sé que le va a ir
well for him Now he has his projects and I know
bien encima Ahora tiene sus proyectos y
that he is going to focus more on his work
sé que se va a centrar más en su trabajo
and that makes me happy and that is
y eso me hace feliz y con eso me es
enough for me And by the way, surely  let's
suficiente Y por cierto seguramente
hear more about the subject because they are
escuchemos más del tema porque están
founding on Twitter
fundando por Twitter
Although first we climbed porlock to
Aunque primero trepamos porlock para
gain fame we threw like used cinemas at that
ganar famita tiramos como cines usado al
[ __ ] face and then we threw ourselves at the
cara [__] ese para después tirarnos al
[ __ ] Carch now Carch will not be
[__] del carch ahora carch no le
worth a [ __ ] [ __ ] and we decided to
valdrá para una [__] [__] y decidimos
look for another victim to see who
buscar otra víctima a ver a quién se
this time the [ __ ] Abi [ __ ] let's see
[__] esta vez la [__] de Abi a ver Es
This also seems super
que esto también me parece super
gratuitous to me because right now there are no
gratuito porque es que ahora mismo no
indications of anything I mean there is no the
hay indicios de nada O sea no hay lo
first thing is that this is a lack of respect
primero que esto es una falta de respeto
and here he is insulting her but very
y aquí la está insultando pero muy
gratuitously Because right now the
gratuitamente Porque ahora mismo la
girl has not done
chavala no ha hecho
anything I mean literally right now
nada O sea literalmente ahora mismo
Calm down darichi because the girl has
Cálmate darichi porque es que la chavala
not done anything at the moment nor do we
no ha hecho nada de momento ni ni
have any indications me because of her profile
tenemos ningún indicio yo por su perfil
no I mean because of the girl's profile Because of
no O sea por el perfil de la chica Por
her way of being not
su forma de ser no por
because of the type of girl no that she is no because of
la por el tipo de de chica no que es no
the profile of the girl that she is no I have
por el perfil de chica que es no de
always thought that the day that she and
siempre he pensado que el día que ella y
he broke up then funa would come from
él cortasen pues que se vendría funa por
her I mean she has pulled out H she pulled
parte de ella o sea le ha sacado H le ha
out all the numbers she has sunk the kid's
sacado todos los números la hundido la
career  because well that
carrera al chaval porque bueno eso de le
has ruined the kid's career I think
ha hundido la carrera al chaval Yo creo
the kid has also left himself there
que el chaval también se ha dejado ahí
he is very much to blame because I would not
tiene mucha culpa él porque yo no
let a partner interfere in my
dejaría que una pareja se metiera en mi
work in my case and affect how I
trabajo en mi afectara en lo en como yo
carry out my work you know what I mean, there is a
llevo mi trabajo me entiendes o sea haí
lot of The Movida that happened with Auron and
mucha de La Movida que pasó con auron y
all that, I already said yesterday no that the subject is
demás ya lo dije ayer no que el tema ya
over and and and and they also talked
pasó y y y y ellos también hablaron
carchis and Auron talked no no they are not going to get
carchis y auron hablaron no no no van a
back together do the same thing but they are on a
volver hac lo mismo pero están de manera
cordial basis no and And such But for me
cordial no y Y tal Pero para mí ahí
Abi had a lot of influence there and caused a lot of [ __ ]
influyó mucho Abi y metió mucha caquita
between Auron and carche Javi and we have
entre auron Y carche Javi y eso lo hemos
seen that
visto
okay But well he also let himself go
vale Pero bueno que también él se dejó
he also let himself sink okay And he
también él se dejó hundir vale Y él
betrayed Auron based on that H now
traicionó a auron en base a eso H ahora
well as of today they announced the breakup
bien a día de hoy anunciaron la ruptura
yesterday or the day before yesterday I don't know the day before yesterday
ayer o antes de ayer No sé antes de ayer
I think it was no and as of today we
creo que fue no y a día de hoy no
also have no indication that there has
tenemos tampoco ningún indicio de que
been an infidelity as
haya habido una infidelidad como estáis
some of you are putting in the chat or or that he
poniendo alguno en el chat o o que él
what can I tell you or that she  I've used it, I
qué te digo yo o que ella lo haya usado
've left it maybe
lo haya dejado tirado a lo mejor de
suddenly because they
repente pues se han dado cuenta a los
both realized before moving in that before taking
dos antes de mudarse de que antes de dar
that step that they weren't that
ese paso que no estaban tan
in love we don't know let's let
enamorados no lo sabemos vamos a dejar
time pass and we'll see we'll start to
que pase el tiempo y ya veremos lo vamos
notice eh but as I tell you
a ir notando eh pero ya os digo así
seeing them both on video seeing them
viéndolos a los dos en vídeo viéndolos a
both on video when I read the
los dos en vídeo en el cuando leí el
statement when we read the statement
comunicado cuando leímos el comunicado
Yesterday I got the impression that well
Ayer me dio la impresión de que bueno
good vibes they broke up but now
Buen rollo lo han dejado pero ahora
seeing them both on videos the way that
viéndolos a los dos en vídeos la manera
the body language they had
que el lenguaje corporal que han tenido
gives me the feeling that there was
me da la sensación de que buen buen buen
n't a good good good vibes eh Of course if I
buen rollo no ha habido eh Claro si yo
have broken up Ah you know that he has
lo hemos dejado Ah ya sabéis que pues él
been very bad lately and we
ha estado muy mal últimamente y
decided that it was better for him to focus
decidimos que era mejor que se centrase
on his uh situation I mean they
en su eh situación O sea que la han
broke up because he was very bad
dejado porque él estaba muy mal
lately and they decided that it was better for him to
últimamente y han decidido que era mejor
focus on his situation but if it
que se centrase en su situación pero si
's precisely when he was at his
es que precisamente ya cuando estuvo
worst carche I imagine not when
peor carche me imagino no cuando le
people were giving him when he was at his
estaban dando la gente cuando estuvo
worst I imagine that he means
peor me imagino que se refiere a que
when he was being criticized a lot no  they were really hard on him
cuando ha sido muy criticado no que le
and all that and apparently
daban mucha caña y tal no y por lo visto
the kid has had a really bad time with the
El chaval la ha pasado muy mal con las
criticism okay but HM now now he's at
críticas vale pero HM ahora ahora está
his best again no I mean maybe
en su mejor momento otra vez no O sea a
the audio in the videos is too
lo mejor el audio de los vídeos está muy
loud let's see maybe he's not at his
fuerte a ver a lo mejor no está en su
Prime which his Prime was back then
Prime que su Prime fue en aquella época
no but now he's at another good moment
no pero ahora está en otro buen momento
no the hate is over the criticism is over
no ya el hate pasó las críticas pasaron
because the issue is over No the issue is
porque ya el tema pasó No ya el tema se
behind last year
quedó atrás del año pasado
eh I mean the first thing is that the
eh o sea lo primero es que ya la
explanation he gives no longer makes
explicación sí que da ya no tiene
sense eh Because the explanation he
sentido eh Porque la explicación que
's giving is that he's leaving because
está dando es que lo está dejando porque
he's superm and it's like [ __ ] if that's where you have to be not
él está superm y es como [__] si es que
where you
ahí es donde tienes que estar no donde
most have to be not when you're
más tienes que estar no cuando estás
super bad no eh but but it's
super mal no eh pero pero es que
precisely now and he goes and
precisamente ahora y va y lo
has it in coi look you're putting it in
tiene en coi mira lo estáis poniendo en
the chat and now he's going to be at the evening
el chat y ahora va a estar en la velada
Which will also be a good time not
Que también será un un buen momento no
for him not a good
para él no una buena
experience
experiencia
and that each one went their own way that doesn't
y que cada uno fuese por su lado eso no
mean that now we're going to
quiere decir que ahora nos vayamos a
kill each other it doesn't mean that now I mean since
matar no quiere decir que ahora o sea
he's not well it's best that
que como él está mal lo mejor es que
each one of us go
cada uno vayamos por su lado vayamos a
on his side let's start taking out clips of It's that it's that he's that she's that such Not at all, I love Carlos very much and I will always love him Carlos and I have left it weird okay before couples were there to support each other in bad times
para apoyarse en los malos momentos
now the one with the broken toy if it doesn't work for me I'll
ahora la del juguete roto si no me sirve
throw it away when I have nothing more to squeeze bye
lo tiro cuando no tuvo más que exprimir
her cube succubus
le chao su cubo sucubo de
championship and this is the twi that she has
campeonato y este es el twi que ha
posted it really are the visi years these
puesto é de verdad los años visi estos
have something that comes out well for me
tienen algo que me sale bien
everything has been
todo
saying for a week that she is returning to
lleva una semana diciendo que vuelve a
her
su
Prime yes it could be that it is the attitude of
Prime sí puede ser que sea la actitud de
carche of these moments the typical
carche de estos momentos la típica
attitude
actitud
of acting tough you know the typical
de de hacerte el Duro sabes la típica
attitude like that of not showing
actitud así de de de no Mostrar
weakness of perfect it suits me
debilidad de de perfecto me viene de
great that they leave me No but in reality if
lujo que me dejen No pero en realidad si
she wanted
ella quisiera
HM she would have it I don't know the truth I don't
HM lo tendría no sé la verdad no lo
know him that much I warned cares of the
conozco tanto avisé a cares de la
debacle of what a woman like Abi was going to do to him
debacle de lo que una mujer como Abi iba
but he didn't listen and insulted
a hacerle pero no hizo caso e insultó a
reven for
reven por
defending her 10 months later as always
defenderla 10 meses después como siempre
when bticino something time ends up Proving me
que bticino algo el tiempo acaba Dándome
right
razón
with Mariana who doesn't  quiele and Abi what do you
al Mariana que no quiele y Abi qué
think about your participation in the evening
piensas de tu participación en la velada
eh guys this is already there are a lot of
eh chavales que esto ya ya hay muchas
questions lately and so on and I
preguntas últimamente y demás y ayer lo
talked to her about it yesterday night and this
lo hablé con ella por la noche y esta
morning and we've already spoken to her and everything's fine
mañana y le hemos hablado ya y todo bien
okay but April and I have
vale pero abril y yo hace ya tres
n't been together for three weeks now okay we
semanas que no estamos juntos vale lo
left it a week before the move
dejamos a una semana de la de la mudanza
and that's it I wish her the best and that's it so you
y y ya está que la deseo lo mejor y fin
stop asking and so on okay I'm
para que dejes de preguntar y demás vale
not going to make a show or bring
no voy a hacer ni ningún espectáculo ni
it up again or anything because it's
lo voy a volver a sacar ni nada porque
not a topic that I want to do right now
no es un tema que quiera hacer ahora
or content about it or anything like
mismo ni contenido de ello ni nada de
that and I don't want it to drag on
eso ni tampoco quiero que se alargue
okay But those of you who
vale Pero eso que ya lo sepáis los que
are here who are from my community already know
estáis aquí los que sois de mi comunidad
okay it's one no it's okay you can
vale es una no no pasa nada podéis
ask personal things but what
preguntar cosas personales pero que no
I mean is that now this topic is settled you
que me refiero que ya este tema zanjado
know what I'm telling you I don't want to
sabes lo que te digo que no quiero
drag it out nor do I want to talk about the
alargarlo ni tampoco quiero hablar del
subject or anything simply well we
tema ni nada simplemente pues eso lo
talked about it yesterday night and in the
hablamos ayer por la noche y por la
morning and we have decided that without
mañana y hemos decidido que eso que sin
giving any more explanations or anything turn up
dar más explicaciones ni nada Súbele un
the audio of the video a little more I'm going to send
poco más el audio del vídeo voy a mandar
go [ __ ] yourself eh I'm going to send you guys
a tomar por culo eh os voy a mandar ya
a little bit to [ __ ] yourself
un poco a tomar por culito
eh That's it, no need, this is our
eh Ya está no hace falta es nuestra vida
private life Do you have a psychological problem Do you have a
privada tienes algún problema
psychological problem You came
psicológico entraste
to the party just to see if they would
a la velada solo para ver si te volvían
see you again A couple of flies Bad friend, sold out
a ver un par de moscas mal amigo vendido
and
y
failed
fracasado
Auron no but I
auron no pero o
mean do you
sea de
really have it
verdad lo
Listen to me okay Don't pay money for
escúchame vale No pagues dinero en
subscriptions Pay it to a psychologist, to a psychologist
suscripciones págalo en un psicólogo en
sorry and I have to
un psicólogo perdón y yo tengo que
pay it to a speech therapist But you to a
pagarlo en un logopeda Pero tú en un
psychologist okay please I'm telling you as a
psicólogo vale por favor te lo digo como
personal recommendation okay Ah I want to
recomendación personal vale Ah quiero
tell you I'm telling you now genuinely like I don't care I'm going to take you I'm going to
decirte te lo digo ya genuinamente en
put the
vale Yo voy a [__] te voy a poner el
profile and I'm going to put it there fries you
perfil y te lo voy a poner ahí frigos tú
don't count don't post nonsense That
no cuentas no pongas tonterías Que a ti
what you like is to appear on
lo que te gusta es aparecer en
screen Yes no yes you didn't see the bif that
pantall Si no si no viste el bif que te
Lola Montero threw at you Who is Lola Montero
tiró Lola Montero Quién es Lola Montero
Lola Montero Lola Montero Well you don't
Lola Montero Lola Montero Bueno tú no me
[ __ ] with me another other no don't
jodas otra otra no no me
[ __ ] with me the witch
jodas la bruja
Lola this lady at me [ __ ] Lola
Lola esta señora me ti [__] Lola
Montero Lola Montero has thrown [ __ ]
Montero Lola Montero le ha tirado [__]
at
al
karches Lola Montero has thrown at
karches Lola Montero le ha tirado al
But that what multiverse is this
Pero eso eso que multiverso es esta
lady has thrown [ __ ] at me I believe it the
señora me ha tirado [__] me lo creo la
lady who sang the one about the filthy rat
señora que cantaba la de rata inmunda
Two-legged rat has scared me I don't
Rata de dos patas me ha tirado mieda no
believe it I lick it
me lo creo lo lamo
all over 4 years ago
entero 4 años ha
[Music]
[Música]
no no
no
no man I lick it
no tío lo lamo
[Music]
[Música]
all over a phoenix because according to him it will be
entero un ave fénix porque según el
reborn as
renacera como
a Yeah sure The kid will have the The
una Sí claro El chaval tendrá la El
kid The kid will have the
chaval El chaval tendrá
The kid will have the thing to return to I mean
la El chaval tendrá la cosa de volver a
realize that he's been
O sea que daros cuenta que ha estado
like super high dude 1 million
como super alto tío 1 millón de
Followers
Seguidores
1.300000
1,300000
1.300000 followers on
1,300000 seguidores en
Twitch I mean you know what that is dude
Twitch o sea sabéis lo que es eso tío de
suddenly because I
repente porque yo
don't because I
no porque yo
don't stream I mean if I already look at you
noo streaming o sea si yo ya fíjate tú
no if I already with everything I have I
no si yo ya con todo lo que tengo ya
feel like I have a lot dude I've been
siento que tengo muchísimo tío
streaming for 4 years LoL Montero [ __ ] on your
streamings LoL Montero me cago en tu
[ __ ] mother where is this [ __ ]
[__] madre dónde está el [__] este
who put him H the two I lick it
quién lo ha puesto H la dos lo lamo
all over  Dude, how I licked it Eh, I ate it
entero tío cómo lo he lamido Eh me lo he
eh Let's see, Luar is telling me
eh A ver es que me está diciendo luar
that we should look at
que miremos
Juan
lo de Juan
Guarnizo's thing independently because he's gotten really strong
guarnizo porque se ha puesto muy fuerte
you're against Seling for having a
estás en contra de seling por opinar
different opinion no Dante I'm going to tell you
diferente no Dante te voy a decir una
something let's see I'm going to put the
cosa a ver voy a volver a poner el
context back in okay in case
contexto vale por si
[Music]
[Música]
someone I'm going to put the context back
alguien voy a volver a poner el contexto
in case someone is entering this
por si alguien está entrando en este
excerpt without knowing what we're
extracto sin saber de lo que estamos
talking about okay
hablando vale
eh we're talking about Seling is no longer
eh estamos hablando de Ya no está en
trending Selin is
tendencia
no longer trending
seling ya no está en tendencia la
now there's
selin ahora está el
Shokas now there's
shokas ahora está el
Shokas And what did
shokas Y qué ha dicho el
Shokas say Argentinians and Mexicans you are
shokas argentinos y mexicanos estáis
truly making a fool of yourself
haciendo un ridículo histórico de verdad
With how much I love you you know that
Con lo mucho que os quiero sabéis que os
I love you Argentinians and Mexicans and you
quiero mucho argentinos y mexicanos y
know that there is zero xenophobia my
sabéis que hay cero xenofobia mis
words are the [ __ ] truth what I
palabras es la [__] verdad lo que os
'm
estoy
telling you control your [ __ ]
diciendo controlad vuestros [__]
manners because you are making a fool of yourself in a
modales porque hacéis un ridículo
historical way and you are leaving the country in the
histórico y dejáis al país por los
ground and it's you with all the
suelos y sois vosotros con pelos y
details and it's wrong that you do that your
señales y está mal que hagáis eso su
behavior  disgusting and despicable
comportamiento asqueroso y despreciable
you are [ __ ] disgusting
dais [__]
Well then it comes similar to what
asco Bueno pues viene a parecerse a lo
Celin is saying no let's see And what
que está diciendo celin no a ver Y qué
Juan said I didn't want to talk about the subject so quickly
dijo Juan no quería hablar tan rápido
but I'm going to talk about it now
del tema pero lo voy a hablar ahora a mí
what seems like a complete barbarity to me
lo que me parece una completa barbaridad
is that that type of message can be given
es que se pueda dar ese tipo de mensaje
live and that
ya en directo y que no pase
absolutely nothing happens and that there are even
absolutamente nada y que incluso haya
people who
gente que lo
applaud it I think that the message that
aplauda yo creo que eso el mensaje que
she gave today is clearly an
dio ella el día de hoy claramente es una
incitement to hatred that does divide
incitación al odio eso sí que divide
communities not like what they
comunidades no como lo que nos echaron
blamed on me, Sprint and ded a
la culpa a mí a Sprint y a ded hace un
couple of weeks ago and apart from all that it does
par de semanas y aparte de todo eso si
seem to me to have xenophobic overtones it's not
me parece con tintes xenofóbicos no está
right to say all the people of such a country I don't like it there's
bien decir toda la gente de tal país me
no way you don't
cae mal no hay manera en la que no
come off as a racist saying that there's
quedes como un racista diciendo eso es
no
que no hay
way There's no way and I find it
manera No hay manera y me parece
impressive that in today's internet we
impresionante que en el internet actual
are normalizing those types of comments more and more But it's not going to
estemos normalizando más Pero no vaya a
be any other stupid thing that a
ser cualquier otra estupidez que diga un
content creator says or any other
creador de contenido o cualquier otra
stupid thing that doesn't hurt
cosa estúpida que no le hace daño a
anyone because we make a [ __ ] scandal
nadie porque hacemos un [__] escándalo
but in  The truth is, it seems completely
pero en verdad me parece una completa
crazy to me that we are increasingly normalizing
locura que cada vez normalicemos más
turning on the camera and making a
prender la cámara y soltar un comentario
xenophobic comment. It seems like an outrage to me. It
xenofóbico me parece una barbaridad me
seems like [ __ ] crazy. And it is not right on both
parece una [__] locura Y no está bien de
sides. It is not right that
parte y parte no está bien que de España
comments like this come out of Spain and it is not
salgan comentarios así y tampoco está
right that suddenly, in defense mode,
bien que de repente en modo de defensa
we in Latin America make
nosotros en Latinoamérica soltemos
comments about the Spanish for the
comentarios hacia los españoles por lo
same reason, it is not right. It is what I said
mismo no está bien Es lo que yo dije
yesterday. It does not have to be a battle of
ayer no tiene que ser una batalla de
xenophobia, to be xenophobic and racist.
xenofobia que sea xenofóbico y racista
Whoever is xenophobic and racist, this ibay
el que es xenofóbico y racista esto ibay
knows that he caused it, eh, I mean, he
sabe que lo ha provocado eh o sea él
knows the conflict that I know
sabe el conflicto que
this is already part of the plans for the
se esto ya entra en los planes de la
promotion of the evening. Okay, I mean, the
promoción de la velada vale o sea la
evening is selling in haxter
velada es seling in haxter
against lana and amaiz
contra lana y amaiz
agn against carrera
agn contra carrera
selao with him, I
selao cont
mean, everything, everything, it is a war
el o sea todo todo todo es guerra
of against miso, everything is a war of Z, latan
de contra miso todo es guerra de Z latan
with Spain. eh, anyway,
con España eh sea ya se ha estudiado
this has already been studied, it has been seen more than once in
esto ya está más que visto en las
previous evenings, okay. And I know yes, it is
veladas anteriores vale Y se sí es
true, misho, no, the virus is
verdad misho no el virus a misho le está
looking for a rival for misho, not apparently, but
buscando un rival no por lo visto pero
yes, yes  this is more than studied it is already
si si esto está más que estudiado se
known What is the war has not been seen
sabe ya Cuál es la guerra no se ha visto
in previous years And this is on
en los años anteriores Y esto es a
purpose this is on purpose
propósito esto es a propósito
that is known is known But in
que se sabe se sabe Pero en modo de
defense mode we cannot act the same and we
defensa no podemos actuar igual y no
cannot make comments of the same
podemos soltar comentarios del mismo
caliber to show that we are better
calibre para demostrar que somos mejores
people it seems completely crazy to me
personas me parece una completa locura
that someone really goes straight and
que en verdad alguien prenda directo y
says that on camera and does not realize the
diga eso en cámara y no se de cuenta del
heavy comment he is making it
comentario tan heavy que está haciendo
seems like an
me parece una
outrage to me it seems
barbaridad me parece una
crazy if it is since friends When
locura si desde es que amigos Cuándo se
the evening was presented it was on
presentó la velada se presentó el día
Monday it is Thursday it has been three
lunes estamos a jueves han pasado tres
days since the presentation of the evening of the
días de la presentación de la velada del
year if on the third day of this topic of the
año si al tercer día de este tema de la
evening you have already learned directly and made
velada tú Ya aprendiste directo y diste
a xenophobic comment do not be
un comentario xenofóbico que no te
surprised that your path to the evening of the
sorprenda que tu camino a la velada del
year is full of [ __ ] I have lived the
año esté llena de [__] yo he vivido la
evening of the year for my wife for my
velada del año por mi esposa por por mi
friend and for different people who have
amiga y por diferentes personas que han
fought there I have lived bits of the
peleado ahí he vivido cachitos de la
evening of the year and to me what it seems
velada del año y a mí lo que me parece
that I think I think that everyone should take
que que creo creo que todos deben de
into account in the evening of the year is
tener en cuenta en la velada del año es
that the evening of the year is as heavy as
que la velada del año es tan pesada como
you  do you want it to be at a media level or
tú quieres que sea a nivel mediático o
as calm as you want it to be at a
tan tranquila como tú quieres que sea a
media level on the third day of
nivel mediático al tercer día de
announcing the fight You already learned
anunciar el combate Ya aprendiste
directly and you made a comment towards
directo y soltaste un comentario hacia
a sister country, don't be surprised that
un país hermana que no te sorprenda que
from now until July when it's the evening of the
de aquí a Julio cuando es la velada del
year your social networks are full of
año tus redes sociales estén llenas de
[ __ ] because that's what you sought to
[__] porque es lo que tú buscaste
learn the camera is that I received
aprender la cámara es que me llegaron
comments in which they threw [ __ ] at me
comentarios en los que me tiraban [__]
okay You received comments in which they threw
vale Te llegaron comentarios en los que
[ __ ] at you I understand the point is
te tian [__] lo entiendo el tema es
that you are a media person and whether
que tú eres una persona mediática y
you like it or not it's part of our job
quieras o no es parte de nuestra chamba
there are times when simply being at
hay veces que por simplemente estar en
an event we know that comments are going to rain down on us
un evento sabemos que nos van a llover
well Juan Well you don't
comentarios bueno Juan Pues tú no lo
always take it well eh you the issue
llevas tamban bien siempre eh tú el tema
of comments and your part of your
de los comentarios y de la parte de tu
job is completely right what he's
chamba tiene toda la razón lo que está
saying here but he doesn't apply it eh
diciendo aquí pero él no lo aplica eh
but if you apart from that don't take a
pero si tú aparte de eso no tomas una
mature attitude and you see all this and you
actitud madura Y ves todo esto y te
defend yourself by releasing probably
defiendes soltando ando probablemente
one of the worst opinions that have been
una de las peores opiniones que han
released live sister, don't be
soltado en directo hermana que no te
surprised that really the next 4 months they will
sorprenda que neta los próximos 4 meses
tun you every day on Twitter  and that they already have you
te tuan cada día en Twitter y que ya te
marked It's that I think that
tengan fichada Es que creo que todo el
everyone has a great example of what
mundo tiene un gran ejemplo de lo que
that type of toxicity can generate and to
puede generar ese tipo de toxicidad y al
this day Marina Rivers and Sami
día de hoy a Marina rivers y a Sami
Rivers are still getting rained on [ __ ] you
rivers le sigue lloviendo [__] tú te
want to get into the same thing you're not
quieres meter en lo mismo tú no estás
ready to get into that nobody is
lista para meterte en eso nadie lo está
absolutely nobody is ready to
absolutamente nadie está listo para
get into a mess
meterse en un cagadero
like that no it doesn't make
así
sense and what
es que no no tiene sentido y lo que me
seems crazy to me is that it's really
parece una locura es que neta cada vez
becoming more
sea más
normal they've already normalized it on Twitter now
normal ya lo normalizaron en Twitter ya
on Twitter racists are the
en Twitter se racista otra vez es la
wave But that we're already
onda Pero que ya en directo lo estemos
normalizing it live seems like a computer a computer a
normalizando me parece una una computa
complete [ __ ]
una computa una completa [__]
madness it's that no no no it doesn't make sense
locura es que no no no no tiene sentido
people tolerate that stupid amount of
la gente tolera esa cantidad estúpida de
xenophobia and racism very few people and if
xenofobia y racismo muy poca gente y si
you get into that mess it's your fault
tú te metes en ese cagadero es tu culpa
look what I expected I expected first from
mira que me lo esper esperaba primero de
other fighters from other
otros luchadores de otros
fighters but but that it came out is
combatientes pero pero que haya salido
that it seems like an
es que me parece una
outrage to me apart from continuing to include
barbaridad aparte seguir metiendo a
Rivers in an issue that has nothing to do with Ari
rivers en un tema que nada que ver a Ari
also as
además como
if saving this message Celin is going to
si guardar este mensaje celin va a
receive an ovation in the fight accent
recibir una ovación en la pelea acento
with  all the fuss that
con toda la movida que se ha
generated an ovation in the
generado una ovación en la
fight
pelea
I was going to look for one thing I
m iba a buscar una cosa
don't know if I'm going to
no sé si lo voy a
find it but it
encontar pero me
sounds familiar it sounds familiar to me it sounds familiar to me
suena me suena sua me suena me
[Music]
[Música]
mm I remember some
mm me suena algún
comment from the Mexican River
comentario de la River mexicana
about the Spaniards
sobre los españoles
also when the subject
también cuando el tema
of having
de de haber
lost if you have entered this video
perdido si habéis entrado en este vídeo
it's because you have seen the title and
es porque habéis visto el título y
you know that there is some movement yes I have lied to you
sabéis que hay movida sí os he mentido
no Let's see I have not lied to you but I have done
no A ver no os he mentido pero he hecho
a little
un poco de
clickbait but I don't remember now out
clickbait pero no me acuerdo ahora fuera
cecita del pastel I don't know it seems
cecita del pastel no sé es que me parece
very very silly to me in general it's that I remember
muy muy tonto en general es que me suena
some comment about River complaining to
algún comentario de de queja de River a
the Spaniards also when the roll eh he is
los españoles también cuando el rollo eh
going to talk to you more about this
te va a hablar más de este
clip than what he said than truly about the
clip de lo que dijo que verdaderamente
fight that is going to give because sister
del combate que va a dar porque hermana
you know it you know very well they are going to
tú lo sabes lo sabes de sobra te van a
break your mother they are going to blow you up if you
partir la madre te van a reventar te
touch Alano it touches you ama they are going to kill you
toque alano te toque ama te van a matar
my daughter They are going to turn your head at
hija mía Te van a voltear la cabeza a
360 gr it is that
360 gr
I would not be so stupid I
es que yo no estaría tan huevudo no lo
would not But well in reference that subject is
estaría Pero bueno referente ese tema es
all that  I'm very surprised that
todo eso me sorprende mucho que lo
we're normalizing it a
estamos normalizando un
lot,
montón
man, for me What does my handsome Quesada say? Thank you
hombre para mí Qué dice mi Quesada guapo
very much,
Muchísimas gracias
man. Thank you very much, king choca, how well he
tío Muchísimas gracias rey choca que
did this. How well he did
bien ha hecho esto Qué bien ha hecho
this, I curse the hosts, he has taken
esto me cago en las hostias ha sacado ha
out almost the same content that was
sacado casi el mismo contenido que iba
there, he has taken out one of the evening
ahí ha sacado uno de la velada
completely worth the evening of the year
completamente vale la velada del año
4th theater Why didn't I participate and then one
4atro Por qué no participé y luego uno
of each one of
de cada recionando a cada uno de los de
the participants, squeezing
los participantes así se hace hecho caso
out the content. Well, welcome
exprimiendo El content Bueno Bienvenidos
to everyone on behalf of Quesada. Thank you
a todos los que de parte de Quesada
very much, thank you very much
Muchísimas gracias Muchísimas gracias
for the Ray,
por la Ray
friend, the rq went to Thailand,
amigo las rq se fueron hasta Tailandia
yes, yes, yes, eh, it was too small for him. By the way,
sí sí sí sí eh le quedó chica Por cierto
Fran, eh, the
a Fran eh la
sweatshirt, I don't know if it's my fault when ordering
sudadera no sé si si culpa mía al pedir
the size, it was too small for him, but he hasn't
la talla le quedó chica pero no se la ha
put it on yet, no, he hasn't put it on, he hasn't put it on, he hasn't put it on, he hasn't put it on, he hasn't put it on,
puesto todavía no ni se la ha puesto ni
the t-
ni se la ha puesto ni se ha puesto la
shirt that I brought him, you
camiseta que le que le llevé
came back sick from Thailand. Yes, the
yo volviste enfermo de Tailandia Sí la
truth is that I did come back with quite a
verdad es que sí que vine bastante
cold, I already had it in Hong Kong and I
resfriado ya lo estaba en Hong Kong y
think it was because of the change in
creo que fue por el cambio de
temperature, I think it was from the  change of
temperatura creo que fue del cambio de
temperature there's a thing dude what happened
temperatura hay una movida tío que pasó
but of course It's that for that first it's the
pero claro Es que para eso antes es lo
Crystal mly thing about cal mly but of course
de Crystal mly lo de cal mly pero claro
for this I think that
para esto yo creo que
before I would have to
antes tendría que
see what he said It's that of course I haven't
ver lo que dijo Es que claro no me he
seen Agustín's podcast I have
visto el podcast de
n't seen Agustín's podcast
Agustín no me he visto el podcast de
in the end he caught me
Agustín al final me pilló
there and I didn't see it but apparently
allí y no me lo vi pero por lo visto
Agustín gave it a little
Agustín pues le dio cañita
[Music]
[Música]
to several
a a varia
people to see and then I imagine that
gente a ver y entonces me imagino que
there I would get the crystal Molly look
ahí pues pillaría la cristal Molly mira
here we have it
aquí la tenemos
no [ __ ] but it's that but it's that I kind
no [__] pero es que pero es que me da
of don't care it's that I'm seeing this
un poco igual es que estoy viendo aquí
thumbnail here and I think this is going to
la miniatura esta y creo que esto va a
be stronger no Agustín 51 exposes
estar más fuerte no Agustín 51 expone
Ari's lies Gameplay Of
las mentiras de Ari Gameplay
course this Maybe it makes some
Claro que esto A lo mejor tiene algo de
sense with what we've seen today
sentido con lo que hemos visto hoy
eh temari I'm going I'm going to temari Look there's
eh temari voy voy a temari Mira hay una
something that I've heard recently
cosa que he escuchado recientemente Más
Beyond that Oh all the artists that
allá de que Oh todos los artistas que ha
greev has brought in the end it seems that he has
traído greev al final parece esto que lo
put this together IV I say that comment is
haya montado IV digo ese comentario
unnecessary because I don't know they are artists who have
sobra porque no sé son artistas que han
wanted to collaborate Well I don't know how they have
querido colaborar Pues no sé como si
also  come streamers like the
también han venido streamers como la
evening and you know it's the little group you know It's
velada y sabes que es el grupito sabes
okay besides that he was going to bring a lot of
No pasa nada adems que iba trae muchos
artists and facts two like a catch it
artistas y fatos dos en plan de cach
would be that they don't coincide you know what brings you
sería que no coincidan sabes qué te trae
to my cousin with a tambourine or there were
a mi primo con una pandereta oa había
people saying no no that they bring someone
gente diciendo no no que traigan alguien
more urban of I don't know what and you're going to
así más urbano de no sé qué y le Vais a
criticize him too that he didn't bring
criticar también que no ha traído a
anyone you know I told him to bring a kit
nadie Sabes Yo le dije que trajera kit
keo to traperos Yes, listening to a lot of
keo a traperos Yo sí de escuchar mucho
trap would have been cool a kito a kito
trap hubiera molado un kito un kito
would have also raised there like
hubiera levantado también ahí como como
with this what I wanted to tell you there is a
con est lo te quería decir hay un
comment now that it has come out that I did
comentario ahora que ha salido que a mí
n't like at all because it is
no me ha gustado nada porque es
literally a lie and it is Ari saying it is
literalmente mentira y es Ari diciendo
no longer an issue eslan which is also an issue of
ya no es tema eslan que también es tema
events in general says I think the evening
eventos en general dice yo a la velada
is the four No the one that plays I
la creo que es la cuatro No la que toca
don't think I'll go if they don't pay me for the trip I do
No creo que vaya si no me pagan el viaje
n't know what the
no sé qué
[ __ ]
[__]
Ari said
Ari dijo
that no no yes yes let's
eso no
see I don't know if literally Hi
no sí sí a ver no sé si literal Hola
Javi have you seen The donation that arrived
Javi has visto La donación que le llego
yesterday to vin and silence Before it
ayer a vin y silencio Antes de que
played we see it we see it now we see it
sonara lo vemos lo vemos ahora lo vemos
now because there is a thread there is a  thread on
ahora porque hay un hilo hay un hilo en
Twitter I have it here in one of the
Twitter lo tengo aquí en una de las
extra tabs I don't have it exactly
pestañas de más no lo tengo exactamente
in one of the tabs but but it has to
en una de las pestañas pero pero tiene
do with this that we were
que ver con esto que estábamos aquí
looking at here because I left it here because there were
viendo porque dejé aquí porque hab
several things but now we see it
varias cosas pero ahora lo vemos
eh clear Ari Gameplay what she said was
eh claro Ari Gameplay lo que dijo fue
something like it no longer made sense to
algo así como que ya no tenía sentido
go to the events
acudir a los eventos
eh if they weren't going to pay for her trip because
eh si no le iban a pagar el viaje porque
if you have to put it out of your pocket
si lo tienes que poner tú de tu bolsillo
blah blah blah blah
bla bla bla bla bla
blah something like that it
bla algo así
was something like that it was but of course look
fue algo así fue pero claro fíjate tú
at that moment when she said that she
que para ese momento cuando ella dijo
already knew that she was going to come to the evening
eso ya sabe que va a venir a la velada
because she already knew that her sister was going
porque ya sabía ella que la hermana iba
to fight It's that the sister was
a pelear Es que la hermana estuvo a
about to fight last year if I
punto de pelear el año pasado si es que
already told you something about the sister
ya os dije yo algo de la hermana el año
last year and It's that the sister last year
pasado y Es que la hermana el año pasado
was about to fight because of course right
estuvo a punto de pelear porque claro es
now I'm doing the math the money
que ahora mismo hago números el dinero
doesn't add up I don't know what like implying that she does
no da no sé qué como dejando entender
n't have money to pay for a
que no tiene dinero para pagarse un
ticket to go to that but then for
billete para ir a eso pero luego para el
the Queens league king I don't know what they're
tema de la Queens leag kingle no sé qué
playing there pin Pam pum the other I don't know what
juegan ahí pin Pam pum el otro no sé qué
all those events there we can cost
todos esos eventos ahí sí podemos costar
that  the sister They called her three days
que la hermana La llamaron tres días
before Ah ama, she wasn't prepared
antes Ah ama no estaba preparada de
before, well last year, it's that ama has already been
antes pues el año pasado es que ama ya
considered, last year
se ha barajado el año pasado estuvo a
ama was about to be the one who fought when
punto ama de ser la que peleaba cuando
it came to
lo de
Muran, of course, if suddenly they don't
murán claro es que si de repente no me
invite me there to a VIP hotel, I don't know how many
invitan ahí en VIP hotel no sé cuántas
thousand stars there are, I'm not going. I mean, the money you
mil estrellas no voy digo pues la pasta
earn and the relevance they give you
que ganas y la relevancia que te dan
being a person who has been the
siendo una persona que ha sido la
presenter of the evening 3, that's what you
presentadora de la velada 3es qué me
're telling me, of course, let's see, I will say
estás diciendo claro a ver yo yo diré
that here more than criticizing Ari for
que aquí más que criticar a Ari de de
saying, like, obviously, I think she
decir o sea obviamento yo creo que ella
can afford it and she doesn't feel like it and she
se lo puede pagar y no le apetece y se
invents the paranoia that she feels like to
inventa la paranoa que le apetece para
say I'm not going because I don't feel like it, what I would
decir no voy a ir porque no me apetece
say to her is you miss out, you
yo lo que le diría es tú te lo pierdes
screw yourself and you miss out on a great event
tú te jodes y te pierdes un eventazo
because I went to evening one,
porque yo he ido a la velada uno a la
evening two, evening three and I'm going to go to
velada dos a la velada tres y voy a ir a
evening four and me and by haven't paid me
la cuatro y a mí y by no me ha pagado
anything, obviously out of respect that we do
nada sol obviamente por el respeto que
n't have and half that we have and I've
no tenemos y la mitad que tenemos y que
known him since I was a
lo conozco desde que yo tengo yo era
minor  when I knew ibai already, I mean I
menor de edad cuando conocía ibai ya o
mean that I have a relationship with ibai for
sea me refiero que yo con ibai tengo una
more than 6 years with peter
relación de más de 6 años junto a peter
jori, these people, I'm going to go because of what the
jori esta gente yo voy a ir por lo que
event is, I love boxing, the
es el evento me encanta el boxeo los
artists that go,
artistas que van me encanta no lo veo
I love it, I don't see it as an obligation since I'm a content creator I have to go and support it and that's it, I'm going because I want to go, just like last year I went because he was fighting in Peter but I would have gone if he wasn't fighting in Peter
pero hubiera ido si no peleara en peter
and I would have gone. He also pays for my
y hubiera ido Igualmente pagándome el
trip, I pay for the hotel, I pay for it,
viaje me lo pago yo el hotel me lo pago
he gives me an invitation and I, I mean,
yo él me da una invitación y yo o sea
the point here to criticize is there's
aquí el punto a criticar es
nothing to criticize, really, the
no hay nada a criticar en verdad la
girl doesn't want to go, [ __ ] what a
chavara no quiere ir [__] Qué gusto más
strange pleasure, I mean it's an event where
raro o sea es un evento donde se va a
all your circles are going to get together, you're going to see
juntar todos tus círculos vas a ver a
everyone you know, you're going to ta ta ta, you're
todo el mundo que conoces vas a ta ta ta
going to have a good time, there's going to be a
vas a pasártelo bien va a haber una
fun party and it's going to be a
fiesta divertida y va a ser un evento de
boxing event, let's see, yes, I'm going to criticize it and I'll tell you
boxeo a ver yo sí lo voy a criticar y te
why and I am and then we will
digo el Por qué Y yo estoy y luego
also touch on that subject, agreed
tocaremos también ese tema de acuerdo en
that one does what one feels like or
que uno hace lo que le sale los huevos o
of the  ovaries of whatever or whatever it doesn't matter
de los ovarios de lo que sea o sea da
you decide if you want to go or not
igual tú decides si quieres ir o no
now we are aware that they are
ahora bien somos conscientes de que son
influencers therefore they influence
influencers por tanto influencian a la
people
gente
Yes seg ost yes
Sí seg ost sies
pu of course but it's that on the 4th announcing
pú claro pero es que el día 4 anunciando
the evening And you're already saying
lo de la velada Y tú ya estás diciendo
Uy I wouldn't pay for it I don't know what a
Uy yo no me lo pagaría no sé qué una
person who is going to be in the VIP who has
persona que va a estar en el VIP que ha
come as a presenter who has been given
venido de presentadora que le han dado
a lot of attention says that if they don't
un montón de foco dice que si no se lo
pay for it they won't go how is anyone going to pay
pagan no va cómo va a ir alguien a pagar
to see that the problem is that she
para ver eso el problema Está que lo
says it does have its point the one here what she
diga sí tiene su punto el de los aquí lo
is saying okay I don't think she has
que está diciendo vale tampoco creo que
fallen for that or said it
haya caído en eso ni lo haya dicho para
badly or anything like that but yes yes
mal ni nada por el estilo pero sí sí
giving the event Shut up I would shut up
dando el evento Cállate yo me callaría
of course Shut up don't say anything I mean you're not going
claro Cállate no digas nada O sea no vas
Ah go because you don't feel like it don't go But
Ah ir porque no te apetece no vayas Pero
why do you have to appear live
por qué tienes que aparecer en directo
saying such and such that's where the toxic communities come in that
diciendo tal ahí entran las comunidades
she might say it
tóxicas que ella a lo mejor lo dice en
live with 2000 people from Chile
directo con 2000 personas de chile
guys I'm not going to go to the evening because
chicos yo no voy a ir a la velada porque
I'm not into it I'm not really into you have Javi
no me va no me va mucho tienes a Javi
oliveira with the snipers there of course
oliveira con con los snipers ahí claro
penguin 1 2 3 subscribed for 4
pinguino 1 2 3 suscrito desde hace 4
years that you think he's a fanatic and
años que tú crees que es un fanático y
what he does is make clips one
lo que se dedica es a hacerte clips uno
after another and send them to a discord to all these people then that's where that point comes in on one hand I know to say don't say it save it on
tras otro y enviárselo a un disco a Pero
the other hand I say you
digas ahórratelo por otro lado digo
can say what you know but also it's worth
puedes decir lo que te sa po pero tamb
No but no it's not about the
es que vale No pero no no trata de lo
same thing it's not about the same thing as today Hey there are more
mismo de no trata de lo mismo de hoy Oye
cameos in this post Hey it's
hay más cameos en este postc Oye es
true there are more cameos in this podcast I mean there will
verdad hay más cameo en este podca o
be some cameos  let's see apart from
sea habrá algún cameo a ver aparte de
that
ese
[Music]
[Música]
m there's
m
one here there's another one and it's for bad guys because I
uno aquí hay otro y es para malos porque
remember seeing it on
es que lo recuerdo haber visto en el
Javi Oliveira's cell phone channel where they
Canal de cel de Javi oliveira que
covered the news and I'm telling you about
cubrieron las noticias que ya te digo
the controversies I do understand but when you
las polémicas sí me entero pero cuando
talk to me about a tournament I get confused and And
me hablas de un torneo me confundo y Y
there I did see that a lot of people were like
ahí sí que veía que mucha gente era como
no it's that it's done no there's no
no es que ya
more kameo there's no more
está no no hay más kameo no hay más
kameo
kameo
but it's
pero
not what's happening today man what's happening today what's happening today was
no es lo de hoy tío lo de
this
hoy lo de hoy ha sido esto
man and this really caught my
tío y esto me ha llamado muchísimo la
attention let's see what uncle Sur said
atención a ver qué ha dicho el tío
with bread he passed the bread he said he was
con pan pasó el la pan le dijo muerto de
starving they passed the clip and he said comma Well yes you
hambre pasaron el clip y dijo [__]
know So if it is yes if
Pues sí sabes Entonces si es si si
Agustín managed to polish that he would probably
Agustín lograse pulir eso probablemente
have a lot less problems in
tendría muchos menos problemas en
general You know He says that he has never
general Sabes Dice que el jamás ha
had problems with latan but rather his
tenido problemas con latan sino que su
problem lies
problema radica
with hosts we
con hostias
already have a headline here The donation was
ya tenemos titular aquí La donación fue
in the 45th minute of his last live
en el minuto 45 de su último directo
Greetings old handsome kiss how how how how how did you
Saludos viejo beso guapo cómo cómo cómo
see what x person said
cómo cómo viste lo que dijo x persona
about you arls okay the message is in the
sobre ti arls vale está el mensaje en el
chat if I
chat si yo
spoke the truth there is  that you have
hablara la verdad que hay que tener
balls you have to have balls very
[__] hay que tener los [__] muy
good but very well placed I have to
buen pero muy bien puestos tengo que
admit it the truth is that I'm going to
admitirlo la verdad por ahí se la voy a
give it to you
dar
to talk about another person knowing that
para hablar de otra persona sabiendo que
the other person can destroy you
la otra persona te puede destruir
How how how
Cómo
No
No
bro heavy eh
bro heavy eh
Uh Agustín knows no Agustín knows things
Uh Agustín sabe no Agustín sabe cosas
what does Agustín know that he doesn't know the people
qué sabe Agustín que no sabe el pueblo
know a lot knows things how not I'm not going to
sabe mucha sabe cosa cómo no yo no voy a
say I know what more or less where
decir yo sé lo que más o menos por dónde
the shots go I know more or less
van los tiros yo sé más o menos por
where the shots go but I would never
dónde van los tiros pero yo no nunca
say let's see I would never
diría a ver Nunca
say Uf heavy
diría Uf heavy
eh heavy
eh heavy
eh We already have a headline
eh Ya tenemos titular
here I
aquí
can destroy your career I could
puedo destruir tu carrera podría
destroy let's see we know that he's friends with
destruir a ver sabemos que es amigo de
Gref we
gref
don't know that he's friends with Gref and we
no sabemos que es amigo de gref y
know that he
sabemos
knows knows things
que que sabe sabe cosas
career [ __ ]
carrera hostias
like that literally it's something to consider it's
así literalmente es algo a valorar es
something to consider it sounded like a threat [ __ ] Well I do
algo a valorar sonó amenaza [__] Pues
n't know if it's a threat but it's not that
no sé si amenaza pero es no es que
Agustín didn't even like that
además a Agustín ni le ha sentado bien
Ari mentioned him or rather Ari Ari le
que Ari le mencione o sea Ari Ari le
Javi there are things that they've told us yet Yes there
Javi hay cosas que aún nos han dicho Sí
are things that they've told us yet there are
hay cosas que nos han dicho aún hay
things that they've told us yet
cosas que aún nos han dicho
eh Ari mentions it very lukewarmly
eh Ari lo menciona con mucha tibieza
trying like a half good vibes with
intentando como un medio buen rollo con
him no no I don't like him I don't dislike Agustín I don't dislike
él no no me cae no me cae mal Agustín no
me this I do that but it's that
me cae mal yo esto yo lo otro pero es
sometimes he's said stupid things and he's
que alguna vez ha dicho tontería y es
like Agustín he's like shut up
como Agustín es como cállate
better shut up better
mejor cállate mejor
or spicy the truth But well I'm not
o picante la verdad Pero bueno tampoco
going to that's what I'm telling you I'm not going to
voy a es lo que os digo no voy a volver
talk about people again as you see I don't say
a hablar sobre gente como veis no digo
names much less you can imagine
nombres ni mucho menos podéis imaginar
any person but it's that in general
cualquier persona pero es que en general
this world this [ __ ] to me The
este mundillo estas [__] a mí Lo
only thing you can tell me is that those who
único que me pueden decir es que les que
consider that they are against an
consideren que están en contra de un
opinion of mine or whatever but the thing is that It's
opinión mía o lo que sea pero es que eso
legal you know it's not happening
Es legal sabes no pasa
[Music]
[Música]
nothing
nada
Uf Uf what's going to happen is not going to
Uf Uf la que se va a liar no se va a
happen because Ari is not going to deimo of this nor is he
liar porque Ari no va deimo de esto ni
going to say anything to
le va a volver a decir nunca más nada a
oin again what's going to happen with
oin la que se va a liar con
that damn take out tiktok Tina if you want to stop
eso ostias saca tiktok Tina si quieres
tiktok eh stopped Stop but if you
para tiktok eh parao Para pero si
want to take out tiktok of
quieres sacar tiktok de
this this cloth
esto esto tela
eh is a bomb
eh es una bomba
eh minute 37 of the live of minute 37 of the
eh minuto 37 del directo de minuto 37
live of of  Agus today is worth
del directo de de Agus de hoy vale
minute 37 more or less I let it
minuto 37 más o menos lo
go the truth if you think about it it
suelto la verdad si lo piensas fríamente
was a bit clumsy on Ari's part to throw
fue algo torpe por parte de Ari tirarle
bf at him whether what magus said is true or not
bf es que sea verdad o no lo que dijese
Ari has a lot of haters and he can
magus Ari tiene muchos haters y la puede
really screw up that's true let's hope
[__] de verdad eso es cierto esperemos
not
que no
What do you think man I know
Qué opinan ustedes hombre Yo es que sé
a lot of things You know So I'm not going to give my
muchas cosas Sabes Así que yo no voy a
opinion but of course no no but the thing is that
opinar pero claro no no pero es que
Agustín has shown it on his face it
Agustín se le ha visto en la cara se le
has shown it on his face and he hasn't
ha visto en la cara además que le ha
taken it even if I
sentado mal si quiera que lo
mention it I mean if I even mention it it
mencione O sea si quiera que lo mencione
has shown it on Agustín's face that he hasn't taken it well
se le ha visto en la cara al Agustín que
that Ari mentioned it
le ha sentado mal que elari lo mencione
because there is something about Ari that doesn't
porque tiene algo de Ari que no le
sit well with him or something has come to him about
sienta bien a él o le ha llegado algo de
Ari that he doesn't like that he doesn't like Lari
Ari que a él no le que le cae mal lari
that he hates
que le cae fatal
okay about Crystal Molly Yeah let's see it's
vale lo de Crystal Molly Sí a ver está
here I had it prepared here
aquí lo tenía aquí preparado
a kiss Nat Thank you very much
un beso Nat Muchísimas
Hi
gracias Hola
guys yesterday brought you a summary of this
chicos ayer les trae un resumen de esta
news from Crystal
noticia de crstal
Molly and Juan won't say anything about this eyes not for fun not for
mly y Juan no dirá nada de esto ojos ni
fun and  there we leave it
coña y ahí lo dejamos
hey guys yesterday I brought a summary of
Hola chicos ayer traje un resumen de
this news from cristal mly talking
esta noticia de cristal mly hablando
about how her relationship with
sobre cómo fue su relación con
nimu was before and after nimu was
nimu antes y después de que nimu fuera
founded okay I repeat again I'm not
funada vale vuelvo a repetir yo no soy
like you delo I mean I'm not like you or
como tú delo o sea yo no soy como tú ni
like nimu who need to make a podcast
como nimu que necesitan hacer un podcast
literally aimed at trying to overthrow the
literal dirigido a intentar tirar la
elite and bring in other people to be
élite y meter a otras personas para
able to generate numbers I don't make that
poder generar números yo no hago ese
type of content I played them all
tipo de contenido yo todos los dí juego
my YouTube videos are from my streams
mis videos de YouTube son de mis streams
playing there's no video in which
jugando no hay ningún video en el que
I appear talking about anyone other
salga yo hablando de otra persona más
than the eslan one I don't know or so I
que el de los eslan no sé o sea Les
wish you the best of luck to the podcast and so
deseo mucha suerte al podcast y así que
continue destroying the elite incredible your
sigan destruyendo la élite increíble su
notion keep going like this because you had no
noción sigan así pues ya no les quedó de
other choice for example when you're already really
otra por ejemplo cuando ya estás bien
messed up To the bottom like nimu Well you have
retumbada Hasta el fondo como nimu Pues
no choice but to hold on to
no le queda de otra más que agarrarse de
there to get out somewhere else because there's nothing
ahí para pues salir por otro lado porque
else to do
ya no hay otra cosa más que hacer A lo
Maybe in the future I saw this too this
mejor en un futuro yo también esto lo vi
that I saw We'll put it on
este que lo vi Esto se lo pondremos al
delo when he comes on Saturday I don't know if what I'll
delo cuando venga el sábado no sé si qu
do with him on
haré con él el
Saturday It's that he told me
sábado Es que él me ha dicho el fin de
weekend I don't know what day we'll do but
semana no sé qué día que haremos pero
let's put this so he
vamos le pondré esto para que él
answers no And if he's animu Let him answer
responda no Y si está animu Que responda
too
también
no nimu gets it for free just for
no nimu se la lleva de gratis solo por
participating that's what I say or what But nimu
participar eso digo yo o sea Pero nimu
has said something why is nimu catching
ha dicho algo por qué está pillando nimu
here I become the next creator of
aquí me vuelvo la próxima creadora de
hate content we don't know the turns
contenido de hate no sabemos los giros
that turn the best in the future they
que da la vuelta lo mej en un futuro me
burn me or something like that I'm done Hello, I'm
queman o algo así ya termino yo Hola soy
cristal moly and I'm going to throw the elite my
cristal moly y voy a tirar la élite mi
love Are you ready then keep Throwing
amor Estás listo entonces sigan Tirando
The Elite keep looking for things
La élite sigan buscando cosas por otro
elsewhere but because say there are a lot of people
lado pero porque di hay mucha gente
because there are a lot of people who say about
porque hay mucha gente que dice lo de
throwing the elite as if
tirar la élite como de forma
literally, I mean it is understood that that is
literal o sea se entiende que eso es
a joke it is
una coña
not understood that that is a but yes yes if they
no se entiende que eso es una pero si si
go youtubers of the
van youtubers de la
elite of the
élite de la
elite have
élite
not believed it Javi No no it's that there are
no se la han creído Javi No no es que
like a lot of people who say it in a
hay como mucha gente que lo dice de
way these are the ones who are going to throw the
manera estos son los que van a tirar la
elite These are look look and now goes the is
élite Estos son mira mira y ahora va los
as it is understood that it is understood it was not
es como se entiende que se entiende no
understood that it was a joke let's see but
se entendía que era una broma a ver pero
to the D podcasts it has gone no longer  is that
a los podcast de D lo ha ido ya no es
Dallas has gone, Bairus has gone,
que haya ido el Dallas ha ido
who is in all these events,
bairus que está en todos los eventos
damn participant of La, I think that he
estos [__] participante de La creo queir
is a participant in almost all of them,
es participante de casi todas las no ha
virus has not gone now, Agustín has gone
ido virus ahora Agustín ha ido
Willy, well, Willy is not from the elite group,
Willy bueno Willy no es de la del grupo
Ricky has gone, he is from the elite, Ricky or he is not
ido Ricky es de la élite Ricky o no es
from the elite sometimes it doesn't depend, no I mean,
de la élite a veces no depende no O sea
people have gone, they are from
han ido han ido gente que son de de
these groups, damn, I mean, from the elite it's
estos grupos [__] o sea de la élite es
a
una
joke here, Escarle, they are not going to find it's
coña aquí escarle que no van a encontrar
true what Delox said in a
es verdad lo que dijo delox en un
little piece, Nimu wrote to me a long
pedacito nimu me escribió hace bastante
time ago because she wanted to invite me to the
tiempo porque me quería invitar al
podcast, Nimu wrote to me privately on
podcast nimu me escribió en privado por
Twitter, he said, Hello, Nimu, She was never a
Twitter me puso Hola nimu Nunca fue mi
very close friend of mine, I had a value on her
amiga muy cercana yo le tenía precio
because a kiss, María, Thank you very much,
porque un beso María Muchísimas gracias
my love. Hey, remind you all that
corazoncito Oye recordaros a todos que
we are
estamos a
100 members away from reaching 3000, eh,
100 miembros para llegar a los 3000 eh
Agustín, Agustín hangs out with the elite,
Agustín Agustín Se junta con la élite
of course, let's see, Agustín hangs out with the
claro a ver Agustín Se junta con la
elite, yes, hang out, yes, we
élite sí juntarse sí
both came from Facebook, for real,
veníamos de Facebook las dos de verdad
I didn't know all the transformations she had or
yo no sabía todo el transfo que tenía o
everything she had really done
todo lo que había hecho de verdad
afterwards  when I saw that they started
después cuando vi que le empezaron a
throwing a lot of hate at her I said Oh gee No well I don't
tirar mucho yo dije Ah caray No pues
think so After so many times
creo que no Yo después de tantas veces
that I wrote to Nimu to play or things
que le escribí a nimu para jugar o cosas
like that because she told me Molly of course You have to
así porque ella me decía Molly claro Hay
play on Stream but now I see that they are I mean
que jugar en Stream pero ya veo que son
if it was like two-faced like they
O sea que si era como doble cara como
said then I would take the
decían yo luego me tomaba el
plunge and write to her on Twitter I would
atrevimiento y le escribía en Twitter le
write to her and nothing would happen if she didn't
escribía y no pasaba nada si no me
answer me okay you understand Right now she
contestaba está bien se entiende Ahorita
's making the sensation but when
está haciendo la sensación pero cuando
Nimu was coming down and they
ya nimu venía para abajo y que le
were throwing a lot of hate at her and that
estaban tirando mucho hate y que
anyone who got involved with
cualquier persona que se involucrara con
her was this they would also throw at her I said
ella era este también le tiraban yo dije
No I don't want to get away from here
No yo de aquí no me quiero agarrar
because I don't like controversies
porque no me gustan las polémicas
so Nimu writes to me on Twitter she
entonces nimu me escribe por Twitter me
says hello Molly Hello hello over and over again
dice hola Molly Hola hola una y otra vez
just like I did and I said no I'm not
así como yo le hacía y yo dije no me da
afraid to answer her because I don't know what I'm
miedo contestarle porque no sé qué le
going to say surely she's going to want to collaborate
voy a decir seguro va a querer colaborar
with me or something and I don't want to because they're
conmigo o algo y yo no quiero porque me
going to throw hate at me Now yes when she
van a tirar hate Ahora sí cuando ella
's down now she does turn to me I
está para abajo ahora sí recurre a mí o
mean she said Hello Molly do you want to
sea me dijo Hola Molly quieres un día
do something one day collaborate with something something like that And
hacer algo colaborar con algo algo así Y
I  I said nimu Look, I'm going to be
yo le dije nimu Mira te voy a ser
honest with you here in private, the truth is that
honesta aquí en privado la verdad es que
right now they're attacking you a lot and I don't
yo ahorita te están atacando mucho y no
want to get into that kind of thing. I
me quiero meter en ese tipo de cosas te
'm being honest with you. Besides, I told you, I did
estoy siendo honesta aparte le dije a mí
n't like how you treated a friend. You
no me gustó cómo trataste a una amiga tú
know that caprimint is one of my friends
sabes que caprimint es una de mis amigas
that I love the most and I'm being honest with you. What she's telling me doesn't make
que yo más quiero y te estoy siendo
her look bad too, I mean
deja mal a ella también o sea
because she's saying that when nimmo was
porque está diciendo que cuando nimmo
frowned upon she didn't want to collaborate with
estaba mal vista no quería colaborar con
her. Or is she saying that she was behind
ella oa está diciendo que estuvo detrás
nimu when nimu was in her
de nimu cuando nimu estaba en su
Prime.
Prime
No, of course, let's see, she's telling it as if
No claro a ver lo está contando como si
this made nimu look bad and it's like it's the
esto dejara mal a nimu y es como es que
same thing. I mean, you go after her
lo mismo no O sea tú vas detrás de ella
when she's in her Prime. Hello, hello, hello, she
cuando está en su Prime Hola hola hola
doesn't answer you, I left you on seen and when
no te responde te dej en visto y cuando
nmu is answering you because it seems
nmu te está respondiendo porque se ve
that the girl didn't have much support, of
que la chavala no tenía muchos apoyos
course, the moments in which she was uh
claro los momentos en los que estaba eh
looking terrible with everyone, I mean
quedando fatal con todo el mundo o sea
at the moment when they were bullying
en el momento que le estaban dando gaña
nimu from all sides, no uh the girl would
por todos lados a nimu no eh la chavala
n't have support if she was looking for
no tendría apoyo si estaba buscando a
people  with whom I had cordiality
gente con la que tuviera cordialidad
to collaborate or to make
para colaborar o para hacer contenido
white content Okay and then you didn't
blanco Vale y Y entonces ahí ya no
want to because it was frowned upon, not
querías tú porque como estaba mal vista
even collaborating with Nimu gets you into
ni a ti colaborar con nimu no te mete
any
ninguna
controversy I mean you collaborate with Nimu And
polémica O sea tú colaboras con nimu Y
if you make a video that's about
si tú haces un vídeo que es de
video games and such no no no you're not
videojuegos y tal no no no te estás
getting into their
metiendo en sus
trouble okay I mean who does this make look bad I
líos vale o sea a quién deja mal esto me
liked how you treated her and she said Oh
gustó cómo la trataste y me dijo Ay pues
well now you've become the same as everyone else
bueno ya te volviste igual que todos
do whatever you want just Come here to
hazle como quieras solo Vení aquí para
tell you if you wanted to come to our
decirte si querías en venir a nuestro
podcast but goodbye and she deleted me I mean just
podcast pero adiós y me borró o sea solo
to be honest and tell her the truth that I did
por ser honesta y decirle la verdad de
n't want to talk at that moment how
que no quería hablar en ese momento qué
ugly that someone wants to collaborate with you
feo que alguien quiera colaborar contigo
right when
justo cuando está en
the title of Juan's live is in it
el el título del directo de Juan
you streamer who lives in
tú streamer que vive en
Mexico a country that can't stand
México país que no soporta
selling looking for chisel Juan eh
selling buscando chisel Juan eh
then then how he got scratched eh When we
luego luego cómo se rayaba eh Cuando
were discussing his issues eh
tratábamos los temas de él eh
what a guy what a hypocrite bottom And that everyone
qué tío qu hipócrita fondo Y que todos
is throwing at him no no it's cool I mean
le están tirando no no está padre o sea
after so many times that one tried
después de tantas veces que una intentó
Now they really want to hold each other's hands  when it's already
Ahora sí se quieren agarrar la mano de
rumbled and I
la otra ya cuando está retumbada y yo
was honest and I think she didn't like the
fui sincera y creo que no le gustó la
[ __ ] sincerity and just when it
sinceridad [__] madre y justo cuando ya
was already rumbled Well in the void where
estaba retumbada Pues en el vacío donde
everyone threw heid at her that Dallas took her out
todos le tiraron heid que Dallas la sacó
and so on she was looking for where eh
y demás estuviera buscando por dónde eh
with whom to collaborate or play because
con quién colaborar o jugar porque ya
nobody wanted to anymore and she already wanted to
nadie quería y ya conmigo ya quería
collaborate with me So it's not right, I mean I
colaborar Entonces no está bien o sea me
felt used and I told her, I was honest
sentí utilizada y se lo dije fui honesta
and I never published it but well if she
y no lo publiqué nunca pero pues ella si
gives space along with another person to
le da espacio junto a otra persona a
someone to continue throwing hate at me then she
alguien a seguirme tirando hate pues
's generating the same situation is that she
está generando la misma situación es que
told me ca she was on discord I don't know I
me dijo ca estaba en discord no s yo te
'm listening to you this is my Supermarket and I did
estoy escuchando est mi Supermercado y
n't want to say what about nimu and you threw her
no quería decir lo de nimu y la tiraste
friend I had that in private But
amiga Eso yo lo tenía en privado Pero no
nothing good happens when everything happened at the
pasa nada bueno cuando sucedió todo al
beginning with nimu we even
principio lo de nimu nosotros hasta la
had her invited to the trochando eye eye to
teníamos invitada al trochando ojo ojo a
this eye to this that this is already great
esto ojo a esto que esto ya es buenísimo
let's pay attention to what she just said to
vamos atentos a lo que acaba de decir a
cing eh Look pay attention to this detail
cing eh Mira atentos a este detalle
I want you to listen carefully J to
quiero que escuchéis con atención J a
another person to someone to continue
otra persona a alguien a seguirme
throwing hate at me then it's generating the
tirando hate pues está generando la
same situation is  that c told me was
misma situación es que me dijo c estaba
on discord I don't know why I'm
en discord no sé por qué yo te estoy
listening to you I'm at my Supermarket and I didn't
escuchando estoy mi Supermercado y no
want to say it about nimu and you threw it away
quería decirlo de nimu y la tiraste
friend I had that in private But
amiga Eso yo lo tenía en privado Pero no
nothing good happens I mean Capri
pasa nada bueno o sea Capri
min calls from the supermarket even though it sounds like I
min llama desde el supermercado aunque
'm in the Setup
se escuche como si estuviera en el Setup
okay but it
vale pero
turns out that Crystal Molly has made public a
resulta que Crystal mly ha hecho público
move that caprim min has with
un una movida que tiene caprim min con
nimu okay something that caprim min didn't like
nimu vale algo que a caprim min le sentó
about nimu but that caprim min has never
mal de nimu pero que caprim min Nunca ha
wanted to tell supposedly because I think
querido contar se supone porque yo creo
that she has told this with
que esto lo ha contado con el
caprim min's consent and
consentimiento de caprim min y haciendo
both of them playing the role of that no that
las dos el papel de que no de que le ha
she has told him because it has escaped her no
contado ella porque se le ha escapado no
but look at how things would be no That
pero fijaros cómoo sería la cosa no Que
Cristal
cristal
Molly just did to caprim min the
Molly le acaba de hacer a caprim min lo
same thing that Leo did to
mismo que Leo a
caprim tell something that she told him in
caprim contar una cosa que le contó en
private and make it public without
privado y hacerla pública sin el permiso
caprim min's permission you tell me something
de caprim min a mí me cuenta tú una cosa
that happened to you but you have every
que te ha pasado pero tú tienes todo el
right to not want to make it
derecho del mundo a no querer hacerlo
public Dallas took it with his balls
público el Dallas cogió con sus [__]
he made it public he gave a name to what
lo hizo público le puso nombre a lo que
caprim min had told in a live
caprim min había contado en un directo
no that  It was the Cocu thing but nevertheless they
no que era lo de cocu pero sin embargo
fixed the
fijaron la
difference they fixed The difference of how it
diferencia fijaron La diferencia de cómo
feels
sienta
that Capri that Cristal Moly made
que Capri que la cristal moly haga
public the bad experience that
público la mala experiencia que que
Capri has with
tiene Capri con
Nimu And how it felt that Dallas
nimu Y cómo le sentó que el Dallas
made public the bad experience she
hiciera público la mala experiencia que
had with Czu the Cocu thing that
tuvo con czu lo de cocu que eso sí que
was important and that had to be
era importante y eso sí que había que
reported or exposed that running
denunciarlo o exponerlo eso corriendo le
put the bandage there fixed it a little bit
puso ahí la venda lo arregló un poquito
no pim p pum no no no and I no no he did
no pim p pum no no no y yo no no hizo
that I
eso se me ha
forgot but nevertheless but
olvidado pero sin embargo pero sin
nevertheless my Supermarket eh And I didn't want to say what I wanted to say
embargo mi Supermercado eh Y no quería
about Nimu and you threw it away friend
decir lo de nimu y la tiraste amiga Eso
I kept that private But nothing's happening
yo lo tenía en privado Pero no pasa nada
well when everything happened at the beginning
bueno cuando sucedió todo al principio
about Nimu I didn't want to say anything and the
lo de nimu no quería decir nada y la
tiar friend But well nothing's happening I'm
tiar amiga Pero bueno no pasa nada te
going to give you more information still
voy a dar yo más información todavía
okay or so tremendous tremendous eh look
vale o sea tremendo tremendo eh mira
but nothing's happening and she starts to
pero no pasa nada y se pone ya ella a
elaborate a little more okay Why didn't you
explayarse un poco más vale Por qué no
do the same with Cocu that to me
hiciste lo mismo con lo de cocu que a mí
seemed wrong eh what Dallas did eh I
me pareció mal eh lo que hizo el Dallas
mean because if in the end they
eh o sea porque si al final te la han
told you in [ __ ]  I wish I could,
contado en [__] Ojalá yo eh pudiera
many times I would love to be able to tell
muchas veces me encantaría poder contar
many things that they have told me and
muchas cosas que me han contado y
streamer that I don't owe anything to and they
streamer que a los que no le debo nada y
have told me And they would be bombs that I
me la han contado Y serían bombas que yo
will tell here that people will freak out but
contaré aquí que la gente flipar pero
well they have told me in private, I'm not
bueno me la han contado en privado no lo
saying it you know they are experiences that each one does
digo sabes son experiencias que cada uno
not have the right to make them public
no tiene su derecho a hacerlas públicas
or not but but but
o no pero
wait But that's not it I mean like the
espérate Pero eso no O sea en plan el
dlas took it and made it public when
dlas cogió y lo hizo público cuando
when the other didn't want it in the end you you
cuando la otra no quería que al final tú
If you don't want to tell them nobody is
tú lo Si tú no los quieres contar nadie
nobody to force a person to
somos nadie para obligar a una persona
tell it No but well that
que lo cuente No pero bueno que salió
capri min came out and denied the
caprim min y desmintió al
Dallas no it wasn't like that Exactly it wasn't like
Dallas no no era así Exactamente no fue
that I don't know what I don't know how much when I
así no sé qué no sé cuánto cuando ya
was already completely sold and now
estaba completamente vendida y ahora sin
however the situation is that Capri told me she
embargo situación es que me dijo Capri
was on discord I don't know why I
estaba en discord no sé por qué yo te
'm listening to you I'm at my Supermarket and I did
estoy escuchando estoy mi Supermercado y
n't want to say it about nimu and you threw it away
no quería decirlo de nimu y la tiraste
friend I had that in private But
amiga Eso yo lo tenía en privado Pero no
nothing good happens when everything happened at the
pasa nada bueno cuando sucedió todo al
beginning we saw it we even
principio lo venimos nosotras hasta la
had her invited to trochando And the
teníamos invitada al trochando Y la
truth is that I had a very
verdad es que yo tenía una relación muy
good with nimu I considered her a very
buena con nimu yo la consideraba muy
good friend when all this happened with
buena amiga que cuando sucedió todo esto
the scam of nimu's ex they
de de la estafa de del ex de nimu la
were when she was a scammer fakes I fell
estaban quando estafadora fals yo caí
for the social networks and believed in the
ante las redes sociales y creí en la
truth of this guy that she was the one who
verdad de este chico de que ella fue
invented the company blah blah
quien inventaba la la empresa bla bla
blah not the ex that I also knew him and
bla no el ex que también lo conocía y
all that stuff So I went and spoke to her and I
toda la cosa Entonces fui le hablé y le
said What the [ __ ] is going on What's going on here it's not
dije What the fuck onda Qué pasa acá no
that I judged her but I took that
es que la haya juzgado sino que tomé esa
truth I spoke to her to say What's up What
verdad le hablé para decirle Qué pasa
the [ __ ] guy why did you do this
What the fuck tipo por qué hiciste esto
no no she hadn't told me anything because
no no no me había dicho nada porque sí
we did talk very often and after
hablábamos muy seguido y ya después de
that I apologized I said Forgive me for
eso yo me disculp le dije Perdóname por
only believing part I didn't put myself in
creer solamente una parte no me puse en
your shoes The truth is I
tus zapatos La verdad te pido una
apologize for me our friendship is
disculpa para mí está nuestra amistad
above any internet chimera
por sobre cualquier chimero de internet
and after that I think I'll never
y ya después creo que no me volv a
talk to each other again after that I liked her forever and to
hablar después me gustó por siempre y
this day it's been like that I felt
hasta el día de hoy ha sido así yo sentí
bad and after that I think I'll never
feo y ya después creo que no me volv a
talk to each other again for me our friendship is
hablar para mí está nuestra amistad por
above any internet chimera
sobre cualquier chimero de internet
shoes eh the truth is I
zapatos eh la verdad te pido una
apologize for me there is our  friendship
disculpa para mí está nuestra amistad
over any internet chimera
por sobre cualquier chimero de internet
and after that I think I never
y ya después creo que no me volv a
spoke to her again after that I liked her forever and
hablar después me gosto por siempre y
to this day it's been like that I felt
hasta el día de hoy ha sido así yo sentí
bad losing a friendship because I don't know I don't know
feo perder una amistad por no sé no sé
who screwed up there the truth is I never gave
quién la [__] ahí la verdad nunca le di
so much thought to what happened with nim between
tanta vuelta lo que pasó con nim entre
nimu and I if it was so bad to go
nimu y yo si fue tan mal de de ir a
reproach her for what happened Maybe I
reprocharle que lo que pasó Quizás sí me
went too far but an apology Yes I asked her I saw that they
pasé pero una disculpa Sí le pedí vi que
were making [ __ ] out of her and and I felt
la estaban haciendo [__] y y me sentí
really bad and a little more or less what's
muy mal y un poco más o menos lo que le
happening to Ari now that it's like it's
está pasando a Ari ahora que es como que
free [ __ ] out of nowhere they bring up
es [__] gratuita de la nada sacan
any little thing to hate her and I hate
cualquier cosita para odiarla y odio
those dynamics less I said in my Stream
esas dinámicas menos dije en mi Stream
Hey I think they're going too far Well with
Oigan creo que se están pasando Pues con
nimu and not just with her I mean I
nimu y no nada más con ella o sea es que
feel like people sometimes bring up
siento que la gente a veces saca mucho
things from the past a lot and they don't know that
las cosas del pasado y no saben que la
people can change you
gente pues puede cambiar
know But why has she caught
sabes Pero por qué ha pillado
nimu you know what I don't understand is
nimu sabes que lo que no entiendo es por
why has she caught
qué ha pillado
nimu says the conversation is on
nimu dice la conversación está en
instagram Oh thanks
instagram Ay gracias
intalla I don't understand why Catch
entalla No entiendo por qué Pilla
nimu let's
nimu a
see
ver
Oh
Oh
Okay Hello beautiful How  are you doing hello good and are
Okay Hola bonita Cómo andas Hola Bien y
you all right first of all I wanted to know
tú todo bien antes que nada quería saber
if you have any issues with me be honest I
si tienes algún tema conmigo sé sincera
value sincerity if you have a
valoro la sinceridad si tienes algún
problem tell me nicely and
problema decímelo de buena de buenas y
I was honest and I think she didn't like the
yo fui sincera y creo que no le gustó la
sincerity damn it or rather why did she
sinceridad [__] madre o sea para qué me
tell me to be honest I said hello nimu
dijo que fuera sincera le puse hola nimu
give me a second I don't know how to explain myself
dame un segundo No sé cómo explicarme
Look the truth is Capri is one of my
Mira la verdad es que Capri es de mis
best friends and I didn't like what you
mejores amigas y no me gustó lo que le
did to her because I've also seen your
hiciste porque igual he visto tus
podcasts in which you appear And what you say
podcast en los que sales Y lo que dices
doesn't make sense well I don't feel
no tiene sentido bueno no me siento de
trustworthy with someone like that because it also
fiar con alguien así porque también me
makes me go that you only talk to me out of
hace ir que solo me hablas por
convenience nimu I told her and there she put me like I
conveniencia nimu le dije y ahí me puso
quit social media and I quit streaming
de dejé las redes y dejé el streaming
What kind of convenience could it have What's
Qué clase de conveniencia Podría tener
more I was talking to you to help you because
Es más te hablaba para ayudarte porque
a friend was looking for profiles to
un amigo estaba buscando perfiles para
interview on his channel and I recommended
entrevistar en su canal y le recomendé
yours so you go because your
el tuyo para que vayas porque t tu
story is unique I don't know what I'm saying to you it
historia es única no sé qué cosa te digo
doesn't make sense or what
no tiene sentido o qué trato tan
horrible treatment I gave Capri I stopped talking to her
horrible le di a Capri le dejé de hablar
because she judged me and got into my life
porque me juzgó y se metió en mi vida
criticizing me super harshly when
criticándome super duramente cuando
something happened  horrible moment but oh well I
pasaba un un momento horrible pero bueno
still appreciate your honesty of coming to
aún así aprecio tu honestidad de venir a
tell me things straight up I value it a
decirme las cosas de frente lo valoro
lot Greetings and she unfollowed me and she
mucho Un saludo y me dejó de seguir y me
unfollowed me from everywhere I mean I was
dejó de seguir de todos lados o sea fui
honest I tell you I was honest with her
honesta les digo fui honesta con ella
eh the truth is that I was afraid
eh la verdad es que yo pues tenía miedo
of getting involved in something that I
de meterme involucrarme en algo que yo
had nothing to do with in all the
no tenía nada que ver en todas las
controversies that nimo had and getting into a
polémicas que nimo tenía y meterme en un
podcast because I do want to tell you they
podcast porque eso sí les quiero decir
have no idea of ​​​​a podcast that they
no tienen la idea de podcast que me han
invited me to right now talk about the subject of
invitado a ahorita hablar del tema de
Agustín and since I no longer wanted to touch the
Agustín y como yo ya no quería tocar el
subject because let's respect each other
tema porque respetémonos
what he does to caprimin min so bad that
lo que le hace a caprim min tan malo que
cristal moly says that she does something
dice cristal moly que le hace algo
really bad to caprimin min and what she does
malísimo a caprim min y lo que le hace
is stop talking to him because it makes him feel
es dejarle de hablar porque le sienta
bad that the other one goes and kind of
mal que la otra vaya y le como que la
judges her
juzgue
No I don't see it as anything out of this
No tampoco lo veo nada del otro
world
mundo
But well we'll put it to delos
Pero bueno se lo pondremos a delos
when he comes okay And what does
cuando venga vale Y que opine
he think then we also have this other
él luego también tenemos esta otra
thing what about things man let's see what about
movida qué de cosas tío a ver qué de
things man we have there's this thing with me Juan
cosas tío tenemos está lo de yo Juan
also let's see I would put this man I
también a ver yo pondría esto tío que me
want to find out  I more or less have the video here
quiero enterar más o menos tengo aquí el
but I saw that the extra went up as a
pero he visto que el extra subió como un
summary So I think we're going to
resumen Así que creo que nos vamos a
find out here
enterar por aquí
eh Jordi Wild Well you know that Jordi
eh Jordi Wild Bueno ya sabéis que Jordi
while the
mientras que se estaban anunciando los
participants of the evening were being announced the other
participantes de la velada el otro
day he put like an emoji he didn't put a tit of
día puso como un emoji no puso un tet de
an emoji And there's like a lot of controversy with
un emoji Y hay como mucha polémica con
that emoji Jordi Wild I was watching
ese emoji Jordi Wild Estaba mirando en
live the presentation of the evening of the
vivo la presentación de la velada del
year 4 and his reaction when IV announces the
año 4 y su reacción cuando IV anuncia el
women's fight against two is
combate femenino contra dos no tiene
unmissable he
pérdida dice
literally says Why don't you put the
literalmente Por qué no le pones la
evening But
velada Pero
well it's a two on two fight
bueno es que un combate dos contra dos
why don't you call it the evening Fight
por qué no le llamas la velada Fight
tournament [ __ ] But what a
tournament [__] Pero qué
coincidence then he'll say they're messing with me
casualidad luego dirá se meten conmigo
when he compares it Let's
cuando lo compara A
see, it's not bad and And if I can I'm going to go and I'm going to
ver no va malas y Y si puedo voy a ir y
be cheering him on because IB
voy a estar animándolo porque IB me
also encouraged me a lot in the dog Fight and he was
animó mucho también en en el dog Fight y
the first to write to me to congratulate me
me escribió el primero para felicitarme
zero bad vibes let's see right man it's not
cero mal rollo a ver verdad tío no va
bad really bad vibes but I'm going to
malas sero mal rollo pero te lo voy a
tell you again the same thing we've seen
decir otra vez lo mismo que hemos visto
before of who we've seen
antes de de quién lo hemos visto
before it's not bad but it really made me
antes no va mala pero de verdad me ha
feel like the [ __ ]  ass that you copy my
sentado como el [__] culo que me copies
ideas from my evening, I mean but this
ideas de la velada mía o sea pero esto
is how it is If I
es que esto es así Si es que yo lo
understand it if I understand it if it
entiendo si es que yo lo entiendo si es
has happened to me that I have ideas
que a mí me ha pasado de yo tener ideas
and I say Hey why don't we meet
y yo decir Oye por qué no nos reunimos
once a week the gossip people and we
una vez por la semana los del salseo y
make a gossip podcast pom it is
hacemos un podcast del salseo pom se
done I mean but a thousand things Hey why am I not
hace o sea pero mil cosas Oye por qué no
going to do this pum it is done yes yes I yes I
voy a hacer esto pum se hace si si yo si
understand that those things feel bad
yo entiendo que esas cosas sientan mal
but there is no other and such okay there is no other
pero no hay otra y tal vale no hay otra
M it is the internet it is the things that they
M es internet es son las cosas que
have on the internet and that's it in the end you have to
tienen en internet y ya está al final tú
try Well I know how to be
tienes que intentar Pues yo que sé ser
eh original or to be peculiar or to have you
eh original o ser peculiar o tener tú
okay then yes
vale entonces sí
clearly yes
claramente sí
clearly this
claramente se hizo
tournament was done, this Jordi
el el tornen este del del Jordi
Wild tournament there
Wild se
was a group fight there was two
hizo una pelea ahí grupal se hizo dos
fights a three against two fight or
peleas una pelea de tres contra dos o
something like that or three against one I don't remember there were
algo así o tres contra uno no me acuerdo
no criticisms there were comparisons with
no hubo críticas hubo comparaciones con
the ibay evening it is not announced the
la velada de ibai no se anuncia la
ibay evening it has a two
velada de ibay tiene un torneo de un dos
against two tournament and it has another fight which is
contra dos y tiene otro combate que es
the I don't know what on the track
el el no sé qué de la pista
obviously there has  been by your idea
evidentemente ha sido por por idea de tu
of ​​your evening yes yes yes yes literally don't
de tu velada sí sí sí sí literalmente no
embellish it with Oh look I'm going there to support you
lo adornes con Ay mira voy ahí apoyarte
no ok no no no he has touched your [ __ ]
no s no no no te ha tocado la [__]
Jordi has touched your [ __ ] that's why the
Jordi te ha tocado la [__] por eso el
tweet is not going bad if I can I'm going to go and I'm going to be
twet no va malas si puedo voy a ir y voy
cheering him on because he also encouraged me
a estar animándolo porque I me animó
a lot at the dog Fight and he
mucho también en el dog Fight y me
wrote me the first one to congratulate me
escribió el primero para felicitarme
zero bad vibes the truth is seriously with my
cero mal rollo la verdad en serio con la
hand on my heart but there's going to be a mess with
mano al corazón pero va a haber lío con
this and it's not going to be on my part because I'm
esto y no va a ser por mi parte porque
not going to say anything but there's going to be there's going to be
no voy a decir nada pero va a haber va
comparisons Of course there's going to be
haber compares Claro claro ahí va a
comparisons heav there's more yes no no more there's more
haber comparación heav ya hay más sí no
okay one last two
no hay más hay más vale un último dos
more the last one out a three against one How
más el último fuera un tres contra uno
handsome What a handsome crack super good eh
Qué guapo Qué guapo crack super bien eh
superb okay Yes it's true that he has
superb vale Sí que es verdad que ha
kept his word that he wasn't going to bring in
cumplido lo que dijo que no iba a meter
famous people like singers everyone
a famosos rollo cantantes todo el mundo
is
es
eh the world of Stream and such So it's
eh el mundo del Stream y tal Así que es
true that he goes and says there will be all kinds of
verdad que va y dice habrá todo tipo de
antid controls yes it's true that
controles antid sí que es verdad que
man at the moment there isn't a mega name there's
hombre de momento no hay un mega nombre
missing some s there's no shortage of sure that
falta falta alguno s no faltan seguro
one  a couple of fights I think are
que un par de combates yo creo que
left, I mean it's not going badly and And
faltan o sea no va malas y Y
if I can I'm going to go and I'm going to be
si pued voy a ir y voy a estar
cheering him on because
animándolo porque I me animó mucho
Dog Fight also encouraged me a lot and the
también el dog Fight y me escribió el
first one wrote to congratulate me, no bad vibes,
primero para felicitarme cero mal rollo
honestly, with my hand on my
la verdad en serio con la mano al
heart but there's going to be a mess with this and it's
corazón pero va a haber lío con esto y
not going to be on my part because I'm not going to
no va a ser por mi parte porque no voy a
say anything but there's going to be a comp of course
decir nada pero va va ha comp claro
wait but the letter hasn't been uploaded here The c I
espera pero aquí no ha subido letra El c
think there's going to be one of these
creo que va a haber alguno de estos
for sure, I mean not these two but there's going to be
seguro o sea no de estos dos pero va a
some name I'm not very well
haber algún nombre no tengo muy
located balls Let's see now I'm going to
ubicado [__] A ver es que ahora voy a
look like a [ __ ] [ __ ] man It's that I'm going to
quedar como el [__] culo tío Es que voy
look like Ah It's a comb uh Ah that
a quedar tal Ah Es un comb uh Ah que
does a two versus two well well well
hace un dos versus dos bueno bueno bueno
buo very
buo preparadísima
prepared very prepared
preparadísima
but if you already posted the tweet when it was
pero si ya pusiste el tweet cuando se
announced [ __ ] and why don't you call it the
anunció [__] y por no lo llamas la
evening F
velada F
t well [ __ ] What a coincidence
t bueno [__] Qué casualidad
eh And then he'll say No It's that they're messing
eh Y luego dirá No es que se meten
with me when they compare it man [ __ ]
conmigo cuando lo comparan hombre cabrón
This hasn't been done before as far as I know
Esto no se había hecho antes que yo sepa
no yes in Russia Who is this this She's
no sí en Rusia Quién es esta esta Se la
[ __ ] She's [ __ ] she knows  and then no but I
tira Se la tira sabe y luego no pero me
really like him I like you come on divinely I'm going to
cae muy bien me caes vamos divinamente
support you and I love that you
voy a ir a apoyarte y me encanta que te
copied me You
hayas copiado de mí
know man say it clearly and that's it and I'll
Sabes tío dilo claro y ya está y os
fight you and and and that's it and then you
pelearé y y y ya está y luego os
forgive each other but tell them the truth you
perdonáis pero dilos la verdad me has
copied me no no this performance today I don't
copiado no no esta performance de hoy no
know But if you already posted the tweet yes you already
sé Pero si ya pusiste el tweet si ya
posted the
pusiste el
tweet Javi Jordi was on the podcast
tweet Javi Jordi estaba en el podcast
when IB was streaming with that
cuando IB estaba en streaming con eso
But look you know that Jordi's podcasts
Pero mira tú sabes que los podcast de
are recorded no you know that it's not
Jordi son grabados no tú sabes que no es
real live no that it's a premiere no you
directo real no que es un estreno no tú
know that Jordi tweets no right no when
sabes que Jordi twite no justo no cuando
that was announced e but yes the truth is
se anunció eso e pero sí la verdad es
like more copied and that's it there were a lot of
como más copiado y punto hubo muchas
comparisons and you wanted to put in there well
comparaciones y has querido meter ahí
Something
pues Algo
else you know you wanted to put in there some
más sabes has querido meter ahí algo de
spark and something like that And you took the
chispa y algo tal Y le has cogido las
ideas from mine no I mean look at what you
ideas del mío no O sea fíjate tú lo que
said no eh it's something that I myself
has dicho no eh es algo que que yo mismo
have said on some other occasion no
he dicho en alguna otra ocasión no por
why don't you give the evening this
qué no le pones al a la velada este
name things as they are was taken
nombre las cosas como son ha sido cogido
from there The
de ahí La idea y punto y no pasa nada y
idea and period and nothing happens and nothing happens and adas he is telling him then do not be surprised that there will be comparisons because of course there will be comparisons because in the little div goes or rather in the deb evening there is a streamer who plays Minecraft and in it and in the
Minecraft y en el y en el combate de
Jordi White fight in the Jordi White evening
Jordi White en la velada de Jordi White
well there are seven hidden ones
pues van siete escon
seen that will surely get in I don't know
vistos que seguramente se metan no sé
how many lines before fighting or rather it is
cuántas rayas antes de combatir o sea en
understood that there are going to be
plan se entiende que va a haber
comparisons and criticisms
comparaciones y críticas
no but that he has thrown it
no pero que se la ha tirado se la ha
this girl has thrown it cono with ister
tirado esta chica la cono con ister
too and the others I do not know who they are okay
también y las otras no sé quién son vale
two against two but it will be
dos contra dos pero será
boxing I do not know I suppose so no that it is
boxeo No lo sé Supongo que sí no que es
like all good boxing Uf it will suit him and I
como todo boxeo bueno Uf le vaa y os
promise you that it will not go badly as If I can I am going to
prometo que no va mal as Si puedo voy a
go and I will be cheering him on fully
ir y voy a estar animándolo
prepared eh Uf I am not saying this because it
preparadísima eh Uf yo no lo digo porque
bothered me that you copied me eh I am
me haya molestado que me copies eh Te lo
going to leave it to you Of course c okay I am going to
voy a dejar Claro que c vale voy a
prepare this performance and I am going to upload
preparar esta performance y voy a subir
later the extract the funny
luego el extracto la divertida reacción
live reaction of Jordi wil when he finds out about
en directo de Jordi wil al enterarse del
two against two is just the title
dos contra dos é solo le pone el título
okay the funny live reaction
vale la divertida reacción en
the funny reaction was not fake
directo la divertida reacción no fingida
the reaction was the tweet it is not recorded
la reacción fue el twit no está grabada
okay there are div videos from 10 months ago that
vale hay vídeos div de hace 10 meses que
say that this was going to be two against
dice que iba a ser esto de dos contra
two
dos en serio
seriously seriously [ __ ] But I'm not telling you
serio [__] Pero yo no te lo digo
because I'm not telling you because it has
porque yo no te lo digo porque me haya
pissed me off a little that you copy me
tocado un poco las narices que me copies
eh I'm telling you because it will it will it will
eh yo te lo digo porque te va te va te
fall on you Ugh what they're going to give you eh
va a caer Uf la que te van a dar eh
Because IB encouraged me a lot also in
Porque IB me animó mucho también en en
the dog fight and he wrote me first
el dog Fight y me escribió el primero
to congratulate me zero bad vibes the
para felicitarme cero mal rollo la
truth seriously with his hand on his heart
verdad en serio con la mano al corazón
but there's going to be a mess with this and it's not going to
pero va a haber lío con esto y no va a
be from me because I'm not going to say
ser por mi parte porque no voy a decir
anything I
nada
'm preparing you No it's not going to be from
te estoy preparando No no va a ser por
me eh I'm preparing the
mi parte eh Te estoy preparando aquí la
performance here and I pretended to be surprised
performa y me he hecho el sorprendido
when I saw the poster Although I saw it the
cuando he visto el carté Aunque lo vi el
day before but
día antes pero
well for sure of course there's going to be a
bueno seguro claro ahí va a haber
heavy comparison That's it there's no more yes yes no there's no more
comparación heavy Ya está no hay más sí
there's more okay
sí no no hay más hay más vale
eh the virus against shelo that shelo is the one  he
eh el virus contra shelo que shelo es el
fought if I'm not mistaken eh against
que peleó si no me equivoco eh contra
Misho but that Misho got injured and virus
misho pero que se lesionó misho y virus
that
que
Well they've
Bueno le han
forgiven him I suppose he has his reasons
perdonado Supongo que sus razones tendrá
and well I don't think it's bad in the end
y bueno tampoco me parece mal al final
look this is still the evening
mir esto no deja de ser la velada
either it's not the sports
tampoco no es la federación deportiva de
boxing federation it's what you're telling me on Twitter you
box es que me estáis diciendo en Twitter
're telling me in the
me estáis diciendo en los
comments that it's that he is that it's not that
comentarios que es que él está que no es
Jordi was reacting
que Jordi estuviera reaccionando en
live but that Jordi was recording
directo sino que Jordi estaba grabando
the
el
podcast just when Ivay was
podcast justo cuando ivay estaba
announcing the
anunciando los
participants I mean you're telling
participantes O sea tú me estás diciendo
me that this is at
a mí que esto es de
night and and and but Jordi put up a
noche y y y pero Jordi puso un
tweet Jordi put up a tweet right at the
tweet Jordi puso un tweet justo en el
moment
momento
because it was on Monday and he records
porque fue el lunes y él graba los lunes
the
el
podcast on Mondays And then the tweet who
podcast Y entonces el twit quién se lo
puts it up and picks up the phone at some point and
pone é coge el móvil en algún momento y
puts up the laugh right at the moment when
pone la risa justo en el momento en el
that fight is announced let's
que se anuncia el combate
see
ese a ver
just when the
justo cuando se anuncia el combate de la
two on two fight is announced he puts up a tweet of
de las dos contra dos pone un tweet de
an
un
emoji let's
emoji
see from March the
ver de marzo sale la
window comes out next week I'll talk
ventana la semana que viene hablaré
about the king of the track and my opinion
sobre el rey de la pista y mi opinión
on everything I saw it at home
sobre todo lo vi en casa
already
ya
mm no  I know what to tell you, the
mm no sé qué deciros la
truth is, I think he's screwing her, eh, I think it
verdad yo creo que Se la tira eh yo creo
feels bad to him, eh, but of course it doesn't
que le sienta mal eh pero claro no me
add up and where is the tweet Javi, they
cuadra y dónde está el tweet Javi
cut that part, Shokas warned her and the
cortaron esa parte shokas la avisó y el
tweet was
tweet
already told by Shoka who was
ya lo contó shoka que estaba
talking to him by message and there he found
platicando con él por mensaje y ahí se
out when he was
enteró cuando estaba
recording and the tweet
grabando y el tweet
So it's very similar to the one that was just
Entonces es muy parecido al que justo ha
two months ago or a month and a
sido hace dos meses en o hace mes y
half ago, a month, I don't know when, the do
medio un mes no sé cuándo ha sido el do
Fight tournament was which is in the evening
Fight tournament qu es en la velada
other combat systems that look
otros sistemas de combate que queden
good in boxing and in which
bien en el boxeo y en el que se respete
boxing is respected but that generate something a little
el boxeo pero que generen algo un poco
more dynamic, that is to say, two against two
más Dinámico es decir el dos contra dos
and the king of the track,
y el rey de la pista
okay, of course, when I saw
vale claro yo cuando vi
this, I spoke to Jordi and I said,
esto yo lo hablé con Jordi y le dije
Jordi, Jordi was on the podcast, by way,
Jordi Jordi estaba en el podcast by way
Jord reacted to this live, okay,
jord reaccionó a esto en directo vale
so you know, eh, and I spoke to him and
para que lo sepáis eh Y yo le hablé y
such, and it took me a while to answer and he
tal Y me tardó un rato en contestar y me
says, Hey, man, I was on the podcast,
dice Oye tío que estaba en el podcast
what happened and such, and I
qué es lo que ha pasado y tal Y yo le
told him, man, you have to see it  From
comento tío tienes que ver lo de lo de
the vada thing they've made two moves very
la vada han hecho dos movidas muy
similar to yours and he says let's see Wait
parecidas a las tuyas y y dice a ver
wait I'm going to check it out and he
Espera espera Voy a chequearlo tal y lo
was checking it out and he was looking at it and
estuvo chequeando y lo estuvo viendo y
of course we were chatting and I said we said wow
claro lo estuvimos Charlando y dije
man IB has implemented
dijimos [__] tío IB ha implementado
two systems that are super similar the
dos sistemas que son super parecidos la
group is very similar to the one with the
peña es muy parecido al
events now to close a little
que tema eventos ya para cerrar un poco
comparisons they're doing a lot the
comparativas están haciendo mucho el
Dog Fight meme not Jordy Will with the
meme de dog Fight no de jordy wil con la
evening in fact it's really funny that they've
velada de hecho macía gracia que han
put up the two for two now we'll talk
puesto ahora el dos para dos hablaremos
about the fights also the king of
ahora de los combates también el rey de
the ring which are 10 10 fighters no
la pista que son 10 10 peleadores no
So it's like yv you're copying a
Entonces es como yv te estás copiando un
bit from Jordi Wild No in fact Jordi
poco de Jordi Wild No de hecho Jordi
Wild put like a tweet laughing Do you
Wild ponía como un tweet riéndose Tú
think that ivai could have copied or been
crees que ivai se ha podido copiar o
inspired by Jordi Wild's event to
inspirar del evento de Jordi Wild para
make the evening he might have been inspired
hacer la velada se habrá inspirado A lo
Maybe by the king of the ring eh the others
mejor en el rey de la pista eh los demás
no because it continues to be what he does
no porque sigue siendo lo que ya hace
every year yes it is an event that I think he
cada año sí es un evento que yo creo que
has seen that it has been successful above
la ha visto que es ha sido exitoso sobre
all it has had a lot  respect and what he
todo ha tenido mucho respeto y lo que él
seeks as a businessman that he is and it is
Busca como un businessman que es y es
very admirable that is that his event is
muy admirable eso es que su evento sea
better every year So the king of the
mejor cada año Entonces el rey de la
track I think is inspired by that it does
pista creo que está inspirado en eso a
not suit me I do not know how they are going to present it
mí no me va no sé cómo lo van a plantear
because I do not know the justice that it will
porque yo no sé la justicia que va a
have that you are facing a guy
tener eso te estás enfrentando a un tío
Javi Jordi posted the tweet when they
Javi Jordi puso el tweet cuando
announced The king of the track not when they
anunciaron El rey de la pista no cuando
announced the two against two that was
anunciaron el dos contra dos que se
announced before look at the times well let's see
anunció antes ve las horas bueno a ver
I'm not going to look at the
tampoco me voy a poner a a mirar
exact times okay
exactamente las horas vale
eh
eh
But what I can tell you and I think we
Pero lo que sí os puedo decir y creo que
will all agree is that
estaremos todos de acuerdo no es que a
Jordi Although he has acted a
Jordi Aunque lo ha actuado así un
little bit gently and it seems half
poquito con suavidad y quedando medio
good it has not sat well with him or at
bien no le ha sentado bien o sea por lo
least for me for me
menos para mí para
what I see eh I do not know if you will
mí lo que yo veo eh No sé si estaréis de
agree is that it has not sat well with him well it has
acuerdo es que no le ha sentado bien
not sat well with him the copy that
bien no la ha sentado bien la copia que
has given him the the mosquito the
le ha dado la la el moscillo la
fluff that this happens happens it happens
pelusilla que esto pasa
many times and there is nothing
pasa pasa muchas veces y no tiene nada
wrong with it It was seen a little it fell badly to him of course it
malo Se le vio un poco le cayó mal claro
fell badly to me it has happened to me you
le cayó mal A mí me ha pasado ustedes la
have you seen here live it
habéis visto aquí en directo a mí me ha
happened to me and this YouTube well you have to
pasado y esto YouTube pues así tienes
assume that look look you
que asumir que mira fíjate tú hasta
even IB copies him even IV copies
hasta IB le copia hasta IV y le copia al
Jordi The idea is like this okay well you
Jordi La idea es así ya está bueno pues
have to take it as if you
eso tú te lo tienes que tomar como que
're good that's it no
eres bueno ya está no
more
más
this What is the extra that you have put on me
esto Qué es el extra que me has puesto
Here it is that I wake up in
Aquí sí es que eso de que me levanto por
the morning and the first thing I see is a
la mañana y lo primero que veo es un
tweet that they send me that puts me in a plan that they
tweet que me mandan que me pone en plan
say that they say that you are going to get a big
de que dicen que te llega una gran
lawsuit I say
demanda digo
Sorry and the context I say can you
Perdona y el contexto digo podéis
tell me the
decirme el
context me yesterday saying stop
contexto yo ayer diciendo deja ya de
threatening with lawsuits man that it really
amenazar con demandas tío que de verdad
is looks terrible because the
sea queda fatal porque es que el
problem is that he threatens one another another another another another another
problema es que amenaza a uno a otro a
another you know like he's been
otro a otro a otro a otro a otro sabes o
threatening turboplane for 8 months I mean
sea lleva 8 meses amenazando a
when it really arrives it's that I don't care it's that
turboplane o sea cuando llegue de verdad
if it arrives at
es que me da igual es que si llega en
some point that it arrives you know what you
algún momento que llega sabes qué
want me to tell you I don't know how many
quieres que te diga yo no sé a cuánta
people this guy threatened with lawsuits
gente este tío amenazado con demandas de
really if they have to have a
verdad si tienen que tenerle ya un
section for him they have to put him in a trial
apartado tienen que ponerle un juicio Ya
Just for javio oliveira if all the
solo para javio oliveira si todas las
lawsuits that he has threatened if they were
demandas que ha amenazado fueran ciertas
really true the state would have to work
de verdad el estado tendría que trabajar
only for him, in other words he pays few taxes
solo para él o sea paga pocos impuestos
for everything that this man demands from the State, in other words
para todo lo que reclama del Estado este
all the lawsuits he
hombre o sea todas las demandas que
wants to put against the State he really
quiere poner al Estado de verdad pocos
pays few taxes to pay for the work of
impuestos paga para pagar el trabajo de
the judges. I mean if he goes, if he goes threatening
los jueces O sea si va si va amenazando
one a month he says or two, it's like he does
a una por mes dice o dos sea es en plan
n't pay enough taxes
de no paga suficientes impuestos como
to pay everything that entails man,
para pagar todo lo que conlleva tío
right, but it's not because he
verdad pero es que ya no es porque la
wins it or not it's like man,
gane o que no la gane es como tío de
really, let it be, let the people do their
verdad deja deja que la gente haga su
work in peace, don't overwhelm them
trabajo tranquila no le
what but but let's see everyone can
qué pero pero a ver todo el mundo puede
file lawsuits but I mean, don't let it be that as it
poner la las demandas pero o sea no sea
happens he responds to Javi
que se segú pasa responde a Javi
Oliveira and tells him to stop threatening
oliveira y le dice que deje de amenazar
with lawsuits that he goes around threatening everyone
con demandas que va amenazando a todos
with that that if the lawsuit comes to him he doesn't care if it
con eso que si le llega la demanda le da
comes and then you see is that
igual que llegue y después se ve es que
Jordi has already eaten Ivai's cake as
Jordi Ya le comió el pastel a ivai como
event of the year Ivai has to do something
evento del año ivai tiene que hacer algo
very nice to surpass him because the
muy guapo para superarlo porque los
fighters he has are the worst of the
peleadores que tiene es la peor de las
previous three but the thing is that I see that I
tres anteriores pero es que yo veo que
think that this year only the  quit they can
creo que este año solo los quit pueden
get to take away the throne or whatever But
llegar a quitarle el trono o sea Pero
what did you just tell me that I should
qué es lo que me acaba de decir que que
leave him alone or rather
deje que lo deje tranquilo o sea que
leave it that no that we'll see that I didn't
deje que no que vamos a ver que no he
understand or rather everyone can make the
entendí o sea cada uno puede tomar la
decision to sue whoever they want
decisión de demandar a quien le de la
and if I have
gana y si yo tengo
[Music]
[Música]
yes yes I can allow myself and I have the
sio si yo puedo permitirme y tengo la
capacity to be able to sue whoever I want as many
capacidad de poder demandar a quien me
times as I want like
de la gana las veces que me dé la
not to saturate the court But why I
gana como que que no sature el juzgado
mean But why let's
Pero por qué O sea Pero por qué vamos a
see what what we have
ver lo lo lo que lo que tenemos nosotros
is a lot of people who say a lot of little things
es mucha gente que dice muchas cositas
about us a lot of nonsense So no no
de nosotros muchas tonterías Entonces no
that I I have a list I I I
no que yo yo tengo una lista yo yo yo
more or less what I have in
más o menos lo que tengo
mind Look I'm not going to tell you but
pensado A ver no os lo voy a decir pero
what I'm more or less doing is
yo lo que más o menos Estoy haciendo es
every month more or less pum pum pum I pass it
cada mes más o menos pum pum pum le paso
to Pablo
a Pablo
1 But not for nothing but because I have
1 Pero no por nada sino porque tengo ahí
accumulated a lot of people who have
acumulado un montón de gente que ha
said a lot of things that I'm not
dicho un montón de cosas que no se las
going to pass on to them and that they haven't wanted to stop
voy a pasar y que no han querido frenar
in any other way but I'm that this
de otra forma pero yo es que est esta
same nonsense we were talking about today
misma tontería la estuvimos hablando hoy
not to Anne  where Elena wasn't
no al Anne donde Elena no lo estuvo
talking about it Elena was talking about it Elena
hablando Elena lo estuvo hablando Elena
threaten to sue don't
amenazar con denunci no
threaten if you tell someone Hey
amenazar si tú le dices a alguien Oye
relax Hey take this off or take this off the
relaja Oye quita esto o quit esto por
good way or take it off the bad way that
las buenas o lo quitas por las malas eso
's not a threat I mean in
no es una amenaza o sea de
fact it's
hecho es
benevolence if you defame someone or you've been annoying someone for
benevolencia si tú difamas a alguien o
a long time
llevas ya un montón de tiempo tocando
With insults
las narices Con insultos
distorting basically lacking
tergiversando básicamente faltando al
honor and that someone tells you delete this this
honor y ese alguien te dice borra esto
and this and this or I'll sue you and they're going to
esto y esto y esto o te demando y te van
condemn you and you're going to take it off anyway
a condenar y lo vas a quitar igualmente
and you're going to spend money on a lawyer and you're
y te vas a gastar dinero en abogado y me
going to
vas a
pay me that's not a threat that's an
pagar eso no es amenaza eso es una
option I'm giving you options that's not
opción te estoy dando opciones que no es
the case eh I haven't said anything to him
el caso eh que yo a él no le he dicho
eh I haven't said anything to him I I
nada eh yo a él no le he dicho nada yo
from
yo de
myself really what nonsense if it is that
mí de verdad qué tontería si es que
then you have like that anecdote
luego tienes como la anécdota aquella
in Dallas of 11 people
del Dallas de 11 personas hac haciendo
lining up for in the end they ended up with
cola para que al final se quedaran en
nothing on Thursday they lost the revan lost I do
nada el jueves perdido el revan perdido
n't know what it is that
el no sé qué es que de
really Dallas made a huge mistake
verdad el Dallas cometió un error muy
in those cases those cases should have
grande en esos casos las que esos casos
been  cattle And the
los tenía que haber ganado Y es que el
mistake he made and they know it is
error que cometió y ellos lo saben es
that it was through criminal law because Dallas
que fue por lo penal porque al Dallas se
felt like he had to go for a
le antojó que tenía que ir a por
criminal record and for I don't know what And
antecedentes penales y a por no sé qué Y
for I don't know how much the the the
por no sé cuánto
Dallas should have filed those lawsuits
el el el Dallas esas demandas las tenía
through civil law for the
que haber puesto por los civil por
right to honor they would have been
derecho al honor hubieran sido condenas
100% convictions the one on Thursday was [ __ ] awesome the one from Win
100% la del jueves del [__] la de Win
michu I won't even tell you about the one you know, I mean if you
michu ni te cuento la de sabes o sea si
do them through
los haces por lo
civil law it's because civil law is always admitted for
civil es que civil siempre se admite a
processing The problem is that what was
trámite El problema es que lo que lo fue
through criminal law and through criminal law it is very
por lo penal y por lo penal es muy
difficult not even to get to trial
difícil ni siquiera que llegue a juicio
or I mean what was the one that got to
o sea lo de que Cuál fue la que llegó a
trial of entity not for that the fact
juicio de ente no para que eso el hecho
that it got to trial that
ya de que llegara eso a juicio eso ya
was already an achievement you understand but like
fue un logro me entiendes pero como que
saa is that of course they put it like
saa es que claro ellos lo ponen como que
no Dallas loses everything that Pon
no el Dallas pierde las todo lo que Pon
loses But because Dallas is very
lo pierde Pero porque el Dallas es mu
bad and then it's okay to tell him those
malo y entonces está bien decirle esas
things man not this Lucía Echebarría
cosas hombre no la Lucía echebarría esta
Eh I don't remember if he accused her of
Eh no me acuerdo si la acusó de
pedophilia of abuse what was it
pedofilia de maltrato qué es lo que fue
but she did  an article that said a lot
pero hizo un artículo que puso un montón
of nonsense what's the problem with
de burradas cuál es el problema a ver
going through criminal court, that would have gone through
ido por lo penal eso eso hubiera ido por
honor court,
derecho al honor por lo
civil court of course It goes through criminal court because they didn't even
civil claro Va por lo penal en pues ni
admit it for processing I think it was
lo admitieron a trámite creo que fue
acquitted but neurofunk is that for
sobreseído pero neurofunk es que para lo
criminal court for them to admit it for processing it's
penal para que te lo admitan a trámite
already [ __ ] great you
ya es de [__]
know for me those If he had done them through
sabes para mí esas Si las hubiera hecho
civil court, that comes in one go
por por lo civil eso llega del
in the exclusives that he
tirón en las exclusivas que lanza al
apparently releases It's that for me because of that issue where he
parecer Es que a mí por ese tema que
says it's not him that I heard it
dice que no es él que yo lo he escuchado
at the end in the audio because the clips at the
al final en el audio porque los clips al
beginning that had passed I didn't know if it
principio que habían pasado no sabía si
was from him or what the hell he said but in
era de él o de qu narices decía pero en
this case the ones that were passed to me
este caso los que me fueron pasando a lo
throughout the morning then what was
largo de la mañana luego lo que se
intuited is that it wasn't for him and yes he
intuía es que no era por él y sí lo
confirms it because he says no no he's not coming for
confirma porque dice no no no viene por
me You know mine is not coming for I mean
mí Sabes la mía no viene por O sea la
mine So what are you
mía Entonces qué me estás
telling me, I mean Look at what he tells me Yes, it
diciendo o sea Fíjate lo que me dice Sí
's that thing about me getting up in the
es que eso de que me levanto por la
morning and the first thing I see is a tweet
mañana y lo primero que veo es un tweet
that they send me that puts me in  plan that they
que me mandan que me pone en plan de que
say that a big lawsuit is coming to you
dicen que te llega una gran demanda
Sorry, and the context I mean can you
Perdona y el contexto digo podéis
tell me the
decirme el
context? Yesterday I was saying, stop
contexto yo ayer diciendo deja ya de
threatening with lawsuits, man, that it really
amenazar con demandas tío que de verdad
is, it looks terrible because the
sea queda fatal porque es que el
problem is that he threatens one, another, another, another, another,
problema es que amenaza a uno a otro a
another, you know, I mean, he's been
otro a otro a otro a otro a otro sabes o
threatening for 8 months,
sea lleva 8 meses amenazando a
turboplane threatened,
turboplane amenazado
turboplane, the
turboplane
truth is that I don't care, it's that if it ever
verdad es que me da igual es que si
comes, at some point, it comes, you know
llega en algún momento que llega sabes
what you want me to tell you, I don't know
qué quieres que te diga yo no sé a
how many people this guy threatened with
cuánta gente este tío amenazó con
lawsuits, really, if they have to have
demandas de verdad si tienen que tenerle
a section, they want to, they want to
ya un apartado quieren quieren que
file a lawsuit against him, just for jav
ponerle un juicio ya para solo para jav
oliveira, if all the lawsuits he's
oliveira si todas las demandas que ha
threatened were really true, the
amenazado fueran ciertas de verdad el
state would have to work alone,
estado tendría que trabajar sol las
sue whoever I say, I sue, I sue, it takes
demanda a quien yo diga demando lo
a month, it takes
demando que tarda un mes que tarda se
months, it takes seven, whatever, but
meses que tarda siete lo que sea pero
boom, in December I filed one against Diego
pum en diciembre le puse una a Diego
Arrabal, no, in November I filed one against Diego
arrabal no En noviembre le puse a Diego
Arrabal, in December I filed it with Loli
arrabal en diciembre se la pus a Loli
Huerta and now I'm
Huerta y ahora
not going to tell you who, I think it's
e no os voy a decir quién yo creo que el
already arrived, I think it should have
que es ya le ha llegado creo que le ha
arrived  already if it has reached him he
tenido que llegar ya si le ha llegado no
hasn't said anything from what I see I don't know if at
ha dicho nada por lo que veo no sé si en
some point I will say it Yes I will surely
algún momento yo lo diré Sí seguramente
say it for no e
lo diré por no
but right now no but okay but
e pero ahora mismo no peraro vale pero
yes literally everyone that I have
sí literalmente a todo el que yo he
said sue sue Loli Huerta there is
dicho demanda demanda Loli Huerta va
another second lawsuit or rather but it is like that
otra segunda demanda o sea pero es que
But what is the problem if I
eso es así Pero cuál es el problema si
can It's that I don't understand what is
puedo Es que no entiendo que es lo
criticizable I mean I don't understand what is
criticable O sea no entiendo que es lo
criticizable or rather I to each one that I
criticable o sea yo a cada uno que yo
consider to have weight and that has
considere que hay peso y que haya
violated honor and that I can get
vulnerado honor y que puedo conseguir
a conviction I am going to go one by one but if it ca
una condena voy a ir uno por uno pero si
n't be any other way
es que no puede ser de otra forma
someone thinks that what happened to Oli
alguien se piensa que lo que lo de Oli
Huerta we weren't going to
Huerta no lo íbamos a
sue But how What Leave him Let him continue let him
demandar Pero cómo Que déjale Déjale que
How is what he said
siga déjale Cómo es lo que ha dicho
then you have like that anecdote about
luego tienes como la anécdota aquella
Dallas of 11 people queuing up
del Dallas de 11 personas haciendo cola
so that in the end he was left with that anecdote
para que al final se qued la anécdota
about Dallas the notes
esa del Dallas se la inventó el notas
s invented it of 11 people look at what he said
s de 11 personas fíjate tú lo que contó
and this one believes what he said How is that
y este se lo cree lo que contó Cómo es
revenant no  that there were 11 people
el revenant ese no que había 11 personas
queuing up to collect claims from
haciendo cola para recoger demandas del
Dallas,
Dallas
well, I don't even know how many chances there are
es vamos no sé ni Cuántas posibilidades
in life for them to coincide on the
hay en la vida para que coincidan el
same day in the
mismo día en la en la
conciliation on the
conciliación en la papeleta de
conciliation slip so that they give an appointment on the
conciliación para que le den cita al
same day in the same game to 11
mismo día en el mismo jugado a 11
people, I mean, it's
personas o sea es que no cabe en la
unbelievable that by chance they summon
cabeza que de la casualidad de que citen
11 people that you have sued
a 11 personas que tú hayas demandado
for conciliation in the same trial
para la conciliación en el mismo juicio
on the same day at the same time, and much
el mismo día a la misma hora y muchos
less that they put 11 in line because
menos que lo pongan en cola 11 porque
that would mean that they have summoned 11
eso querría decir que han citado a 11
people at the same time in the same
personas a la misma hora en el mismo hos
game, that is, the one who gives the appointment, the
jugado o sea el que da la cita el los
prosecutors there have not been very
procuradores ahí no se han puesto mu
careful or the court secretary because she
fino o la secretaria del juzgado porque
has given the appointment to 11 people at the
le le ha dado la cita a 11 personas a la
same time in the same court, how is that going to
misma hora en el mismo juzgado eso cómo
be? Of course, man, they say things that
ser desde luego tío dicen cosas que
you say, the fat one that I have is not
dices tú la que la gorda que tengo yo no
coming for him, what it must be is because of what he
viene por él por lo que debe ser es por
said about this girl who came out
lo que decía de la chica esta que salió
with the conversations to show
con las conversaciones tal a mostrar
all that and such  And apparently that's why
todo aquello y tal Y que al parecer por
a really big one is coming to me
eso me viene una muy gorda
here I am Let's see if that really big one reaches me
aquí estoy A ver si me llega esa muy
But well,
gorda Pero bueno
the truth is that they don't know, I mean, I
que de verdad es que no saben o sea O
mean, there are a lot of people who have been
sea a mí hay mucha gente que me lleva
coming to me all this time that I've been
viniendo en todo este tiempo que llevo
here, helping me, supporting me from
aquí ayudándome apoyándome por la
behind,
espalda
eh, informing me of things, passing me topics
eh Informándome de cosas pasándome temas
and so on because they like what I do, they
y demás porque les gusta lo que hago les
like what's going on even though there aren't many
gusta qué tal aunque no haya muchos
big channels giving me support. There are several
canales grandes dándome apoyo Hay varios
who do write to me directly
que sí que me escriben directamente por
privately and pass me things. They let me know about
privado y me me pasan cosas Me avisan de
topics of I don't know how many and they
temas de no s no sé cuántos y me
help me So it's that and apparently that's why
ayudan Entonces es que y que al parecer
a really big one is coming to me
por eso me viene una muy
here I am Let's see if that
gorda aquí estoy A ver si me llega esa
really big one reaches me But well, the truth is
muy gorda Pero bueno que de verdad es
that they don't know, I mean, I mean, there are a lot of
que no saben o sea O sea a mí hay mucha
people who have been coming to me all this
gente que me lleva viniendo en todo este
time that I've been here, helping me, supporting me
tiempo que llevo aquí ayudándome
from behind,
apoyándome por la espalda
eh, informing me of things, passing me topics
eh Informándome de cosas pasándome temas
and so on because they like what I do, they
y demás porque les gusta lo que hago les
like what's going on even though there aren't many
gusta qué tal aunque no haya muchos
big channels giving me support. There are several
canales grandes dándome apoyo Hay varios
who do write to me directly privately
que sí que me escriben directamente por
private and things happen to me they warn me about
privado y me me pasan cosas me avisan de
topics of I don't know I can't even imagine
temas de No sé no me puedo ni imaginar
who will write to you it still happens No I
de quién te escribirá alún pasa No no me
can't even imagine I mean I
lo puedo ni imaginar O sea no me lo
can't even imagine the truth is no
puedo ni imaginar la verdad no se me
one comes to mind okay seeing what
viene nadie a la cabeza vale viendo cuál
your content is like seeing seeing the
es tu contenido o sea viendo viendo la
cover of your channel and seeing what
portada de tu canal y viendo Cuáles son
your live shows are and all your titles and everything
tus directos y todos tus títulos y todo
that you put out in the
lo que tú sacas en los
live shows it could be
directos podría ser
any I don't know how many and help me yes
cualquiera no sé cuántos y me ayudan si
a help
una ayuda
You think I can tell there are
Tú te crees que yo puedo contar hay
things that can't be told because I know they
cosas que no se pueden contar porque sé
are illegal Javi Because I am sure
que son ilegales Javi Porque tengo Claro
which ones are legal and which ones aren't
que Cuáles son legales y cuáles no
also that laser has two more coming
no también que a laser le vienen dos más
then he says that laser l has
luego dice que a laser l le vienen otras
two more coming that this leads this
dos más que esto lo lleva esto lo llevo
I've been listening to in some clips that have been
yo escuchando en algunos clips que me
passed to me because as I tell you, through
han ido pasando porque ya te digo yo por
Javi's [ __ ] video I wouldn't watch him even if he was dead
puo vídeo de Javi no lo veo ni ni muerto
in the end I mean he puts more hours
al final o sea mete más horas
directly into I don't know how many channels
directamente en no sé Cuántos canales ya
I'm telling you that neither the telesalseo nor they
te digo yo que ni lo de telesalseo ni me
tell me you should watch the telesalseo
dicen tendrías que ver lo de telesalseo
I mean if I'm in the mood to watch all that
digo si estoy yo como para ver too esa
[ __ ] it's those  clips that were
[__] es esos clips que me fueron
coming to me man to have collaborated
llegando hombre para haber colaborado
with Peppa Beltran it would have been good if she
con la Peppa beltram hubiera estado bien
had found out but the thing is that I think she
que se Hubiera enterado pero es que creo
has found out eh What happens is that
que se ha enterado eh Lo que pasa que no
she hasn't been interested she hasn't been interested in making her
la ha interesado no le ha interesado ha
aware okay but the
hacérsele enterado vale pero lo de la
Peppa Beltran thing Peppa Beltran is a
Peppa beltrá la Peppa Beltrán es una
lady with whom he collaborates now or
señora con la que él colabora ahora o
with whom he has done several
con la que ha hecho varias
collaborations or some to throw
colaboraciones o alguna para tirarme
[ __ ] at me or rather and literally this
[__] a mí o sea y literalmente este
man who was super indignant with
hombre que estaba super indignado con
stardeos no and all that starts to
stardeos no y todo eso se pone a
get along with the lady of the 240
llevarse con la señora de los 240
be it a lady who asked for 240 bucks for
sea una señora que pidió 240 pavos para
an association against cancer and they
una asociación contra el cáncer y la
caught her after 6 or 7 months the friends
pillaron a los se o 7 meses los amigos
who sold her okay they sold her
que la vendieron vale que la vendieron
Well the episode of The 240 bucks
Bueno lo del episodio de Los 240 pavos
is one among many that can be counted
es uno entre tantos que se pueden contar
okay but There are
vale pero Son
240 that the lady hadn't
240 que la señora no los había
given then we found out that when we
dado luego nos enteramos que cuando la
caught her Okay when the friends
trincar Vale cuando los amigos lo
sold it it turns out that the lady went at
vendieron resulta que la señora fue a
10 in the morning running to the
las 10 de la mañana corriendo a la
association to give him the 240  turkeys at 7
asociación a darle los 240 pavos a los 7
months
meses
and trying to make the donation
e intentando que La donación fuera
anonymous nothing nonsense asked for
anónima nada una tontería pidió
donations for cancer nothing nothing nothing
donaciones para el cáncer nada nada nada
nothing ugly for a long time what it seems is
nada feo durante tiempo lo que parece es
that those two demands must be one
que esas dos demandas deben ser una por
from Javi Oliveira who has been
parte de Javi oliveira que ha ido
undermining apparently insults that he has been saying
minando al parecer insul tios que le
the insults that
haya estado diciendo los insul tios que
Javi says that he takes one from here another from
dice Javi que coge uno de aquí otro de
there another from here okay well he has been
allá otro de aquí vale pues ha ido
collecting insults that state he says
recogiendo insul tios que estado dice
dedicating that to him he says we will see if in the end it
dedicándole eso dice veremos si al final
is true and it arrives because I say that it is
es verdad y llega porque digo que es
Javi what to say and do is another topic insults
Javi lo de decir y hacer es otro tema
insults already we will see what
insul tios insulti ya ya veremos de Qué
are the demands for insults insults
son las demanda de insul tios insul tios
and that in principle he says that they arrive to him since they
y que en principio dice que le Llegan ya
should have arrived to him I
que le tendrían que haber llegado yo que
know what you know because it should have also
sé qué sabes porque también le tení que
arrived to Turbo 8 months ago but
haber llegado a Turbo hace 8 meses pero
the other one is also understood by the
la otra se entiende también por las
things that I have been saying in these clips
cosas que he ido diciendo en estos clips
that it would be like Dallas that it seems that
que sería como de Dallas que parece que
Dallas and he have met now that
se ha juntado ahora Dallas y él a que
since he has talked a lot about them and has
como ha hablado mucho de ellos y ha
said things Well he says well let's
dicho cosas Pues dice pues vamos a
harass him with a lot of demands and see if that way he backs
acosar le con muchas demandas y a ver si
down, sue like that so that
así se echa para atrás demanda
means when we are the ones suing we
sea que cuando los que demandamos somos
are harassing with demands
nosotros estamos acosando con demandas
m
m
interesting He was also talking about
interesante También estuvo hablando de
my financial situation because I think he
mi situación financiera por lo que creo
was talking about my family, I mean it's
y estuvo hablando de mi familia o sea es
nice that Javi doesn't like to
bonito esto de que Javi no le gusta
involve other people's families but he
meter a las familias de los demás pero
was mentioning mine there not
estuvo nombrando por ahí a la mía no
saying that a person with a family and
diciendo que una persona con familia y
such should be more concerned with
tal debería estar más preocupado con con
these things and if he is not well off
estas cosas y si no está bien
financially he shouldn't be
económicamente no debería estar
worried about things this is fine
preocupado en las cosas está bien esto
eh I mean the thing about Javi getting angry every time
eh o sea lo de que Javi se arda cada vez
his family is mentioned the least
que nombran a su familia lo más mínimo
but then he dedicates himself on live shows
pero luego que él se dedique en directos
to talk about other people's families and
a hablar de las familias de los demás y
what we have to do with
de lo que nosotros tenemos hacer con
our family and with our
nuestra familia y con nuestra situación
financial situation that I talk about
económica que yo hablo de las
families yes he talked about the evening in that
familias sí habló de la velada en ese
live show the topic is Dala and I my son
directo el tema somos dala y yo hijo mío
always the topic is Dala and
siempre el tema somos dala y
I well people I'm going to leave it here
yo bueno gente lo voy a dejar por aquí
eh these topics for newscasts places
eh estos temas para noticieros lugares
we leave it okay it's two I'll see if I
lo dejamos vale son las dos voy a ver si
record you  you're going to have to sue for some newscast about
te grabo algo de noticiero de de
telesalseo
telesalseo
Javi no it's not
lo vas a tener que demandar Javi no no
on my list right now the demand
entra en mi lista ahora mismo de demanda
is
es
that F all these people there
que F toda esta gente allí
explaining themselves I think he's talking about another
explicándose Yo creo que habla de otro
habi
habi
man yes I have mentioned on some
hombre si yo he mencionado en alguna
occasion that this man has a
ocasión que que este hombre tiene
family I assure you that it wasn't to be
familia Ya ya te aseguro yo que no habrá
disrespectful or to
sido ni para faltar respeto ni para
say anything bad I'm telling you Extra
decir nada malo ya te lo digo Extra
extra tweet from
extra tweet de
alana
alana
t from alana alana
t de alana alana
rana
rana
eye my daughter you were hacked or
ojo mi hia te hackearon o
something
algo
guys see you handsome
chicos nos vemos guapos
bye
adiós